<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 13:48:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 13:48:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AutoHideMouseCursor 5.95</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideMouseCursor is a Microsoft Windows application mobile mini allows you to hide the cursor, if the mouse is not active for a period of time. With AutoHideMouseCursor you can automatically hide the mouse cursor with the timer can be customized this is utility desktop perfect when the cursor is too annoying to them, such as when used with the application handling the text because often when you add pointers, text and cover text.
AutoHideMouseCursor - Hide mouse cursor
User...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.1.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:47:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft Prevent Computer Sleep 1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:47:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-prevent-computer-sleep-7686.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-prevent-computer-sleep-7686.html
</guid><description>
Modern hard disks are set to automatically switch to sleep mode (also known as idle time) whenever file operations are no longer happening. This is a method that is supposed to help cool the physical disk and extend its lifespan. However, if you want to prevent this from happening, such as if you want to disk quickly to respond to files of the file even if in the standby mode for long periods, then you can adjust the built-in settings of the machine to turn off.
Being designed for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exportizer Enterprise 10.2.6.576</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:46:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html
</guid><description>
Exportizer Pro is software export base, robust data that allows view, edit and export the database to a data file, text, clipboard. Exportizer Pro is a software tool effective and simple, can be used to help individuals view, filter and copy an entire database to clipboard or convert it to another format.
Simple interface and no complex also indicates that Exportizer Pro meet the system requirements, the application can run on most operating systems.
The main window of Exportizer Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dup Scout Ultimate 17.5.14 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:45:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dup-scout-ultimate-1460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dup-scout-ultimate-1460.html
</guid><description>
Dup Scout Ultimate is professional software with the aim of helping you detect files duplicate is stored in your computer and delete them to free some space on disk. Management utility this file can clean up the file to duplicate from disc, folder, network share or storage device NAS.
Dup Scout Ultimate - Find and delete file duplicate
Dup Scout Ultimate offers you the ability to build a new profile by specifying the name and select the folder or network share, all hard disks, servers...
</description></item><item><title>Download Uninstall Tool 3.8.1 Build 5740</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:45:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uninstall-tool-333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uninstall-tool-333.html
</guid><description>
Uninstall Tool is a removal unique and powerful help for your computer work faster. Uninstall Tool is a quick, safe, and convenient to delete the application and system components is not necessary. Uninstall Tool would be great software to replace the Windows program Add / Remove.
Uninstall Tool - uninstaller powerful
The program has lots of features and options mising in the applet of Microsoft. Uninstaller tool installation works with MAXIMUM SPEED and COMPLETELY removes any program...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3Dsurvey 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:44:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dsurvey-3831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dsurvey-3831.html
</guid><description>
3Dsurvey is a software solution to handle soil survey data. Take a photo with any digital camera standard how to import photos into 3Dsurvey and create a map orthophoto of own models, digital surface and calculates volume faster and easier. The data is processed automatically based on the matching algorithm. Use the smart tool of the us to be even more effective. Software 3Dsurvey this is designed to operate with any digital camera, DSLR, or GoPro. Use any UAV to take pictures of terrain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools 1.0.0.810</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:44:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html
</guid><description>
Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools is a package of ransomware decryption tools to help you get back files from 20 different ransomware encrypted. Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools supports decryption AES_NI, Alcatraz Locker, Apocalypse, BadBlock, Bart, BTCWare, Crypt888, CryptoMix (Offline), CrySiS, EncrypTile, FindZip, Globe HiddenTear, Jigsaw, Legion NoobCrypt, Stampado, SZFLocker, TeslaCrypt, XData.
Features of Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools
	Easily remove ransomware
	Decrypt and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geek Uninstaller 1.5.3.170</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:44:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekuninstaller-1250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekuninstaller-1250.html
</guid><description>
GeekUninstaller is the uninstall the software quickly and effectively on taiwebs.com is good software today. It includes a number of useful features such as: remove force for the application, first, the ability to quickly go to the book or website, see to the installation directory of the application.
GeekUninstaller - Uninstall software
GeekUninstaller does not require installation and runs on both version 32 and 64 bit of Windows XP / Vista / 7/8 and 10. This is a lightweight app...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.18.0.10 + Professional</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:43:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251124</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:42:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allround Automations PL-SQL Developer 16.0.8.2175</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html
</guid><description>
Allround Automations PL/SQL Developer is a development environment integration is specifically targeted at the development application units are stored for the Oracle database. Over time, we have seen the business logic more and move towards the Oracle server, make PL / SQL programming become an important part of the development process overall. This software focuses on ease of use, coding quality and the main advantage in the process of software development, Oracle.
The features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DMSoft DBConvert for Oracle and Access 1.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:42:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-oracle-and-access-11358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-oracle-and-access-11358.html
</guid><description>
DMSoft DBConvert for Oracle and Access is a two-way migration tool that completely converts and synchronizes Microsoft Access databases (MDB, ACCDB) to Oracle Server/Oracle cloud and vice versa. Additionally, you can also perform database conversions between Oracle databases (on-premises or in the cloud) or between two Access databases. You just need to specify them as both source and destination types.
All customizations for the target database are presented in an intuitive tree...
</description></item><item><title>Download DMSoft DBConvert for Access and FoxPro 3.5.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:41:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-access-and-foxpro-11359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-access-and-foxpro-11359.html
</guid><description>
DMSoft DBConvert for Access and FoxPro is a reliable two-way database migration software that supports conversion and synchronization of Microsoft Access (.mdb or .accdb files) to both MS FoxPro (.DBC) and FoxPro free board (.DBF) ). Additionally, data can be saved to MS Visual FoxPro Program (*.prg). With just a few clicks, you can easily transfer tables, records, and other data objects from Access to DBF. The software ensures that your data remains intact and is converted accurately,...
</description></item><item><title>Download gSyncing 1.1.71</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:40:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncing-10173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncing-10173.html
</guid><description>
gSyncing allows you to synchronize your contacts, calendar, and Outlook tasks with your Google account and other supported services such as smartphones and tablets runs on iOS, Android, Windows Phone, etc. For example, sync Outlook calendar with Google calendar. You can easily use your Gmail account while traveling and then continue using Outlook on your desktop. Syncing your Google contacts with Outlook helps you access and manage your contacts on any device.
The program runs on...
</description></item><item><title>Download DMSoft DBConvert for Access and MSSQL 6.1.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:33:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-access-and-mssql-11356.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-access-and-mssql-11356.html
</guid><description>
DMSoft DBConvert for Access and MSSQL is a powerful cross database migration tool to increase the size and synchronize Access x86/x64 data with MS SQL Server. Other move combinations are also supported. This tool provides direct conversion but when you need to overcome firewalls, MS SQL Dump files can be created. DBConvert software can automatically convert MS Access queries to MS SQL Server views without knowing about the differences between SQL dialects.
DBSync for Access and MSSQL is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Approximatrix Simply Fortran 3.41.4438</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:32:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-approximatrix-simply-fortran-9559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-approximatrix-simply-fortran-9559.html
</guid><description>
Approximatrix Simply Fortran is an integrated development environment (IDE) for the Fortran programming language. It is designed to provide an efficient and user-friendly environment for Fortran development, with features such as code editing, debugging, and project management tools.
Simply Fortran supports the Fortran 2008 standard and includes features such as syntax highlighting, code completion, and automatic indentation to aid writing Fortran code. It also has a built-in compiler...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 16.0.58388</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:53:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor 3.13.77</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:52:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-pro-picture-editor-8225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-pro-picture-editor-8225.html
</guid><description>
Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor is a powerful photo editing application that allows users to enhance and transform their photos with a variety of filters, effects and frames. Enhance your photos with over 640 beautiful frames, effects, filters or montages! Photo Lab PRO is an easy, fast and fun photo editor. You don't have to be a Photoshop expert to make every photo funny and every portrait beautiful.
Features of Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor
	Photo effects: Photo Lab PRO offers a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.6.0-2486</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:52:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download Currency Converter Plus 3.1.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:51:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html
</guid><description>
Advanced currency converter - With multiple currency fields, historical rate charts, and a built-in calculator for convenience, compare prices wherever you travel abroad to ensure Make sure you get the best deal at today's price. All conversions use live exchange rates from AccuRate™, providing the most accurate rates available in the world. Plus, it still works offline for moves when exchange rate data isn't available. This app even supports Bitcoin!
Features of Currency Converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.11.270105</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Peachy - AI Face &amp;amp; Body Editor 1.190.55</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:51:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peachy-ai-face-body-editor-13805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peachy-ai-face-body-editor-13805.html
</guid><description>
Peachy - AI Face &amp;amp; Body Editor is a powerful and user-friendly photo editing app that focuses on enhancing selfies and portraits through advanced body reshaping and editing features. The app helps users get the best look by smoothing skin, whitening teeth, removing blemishes and wrinkles, reshaping facial features and body parts, and applying makeup and lighting effects.
Key Features
	Photo Editing: Smooth skin, remove pimples and wrinkles, brighten eyes, whiten teeth, reduce dark...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.57.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:50:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster - XEQ 31.16.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:50:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html
</guid><description>
This XEQ app is a powerful yet easy-to-use Music Equalizer with Bass Boost, Volume Boost, Auto Volume Boost and 3D Virtualizer effects, which can improve the sound quality of your device. your Android device.
This is the only equalizer fx app you will ever need for your smartphone. With this feature, you can not only equalize the bass boost, but also increase the normal sound volume of your Android phone, add virtual 3D effects, save custom presets, automatically recall presets of audio...
</description></item></channel></rss>