<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:08:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:08:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinMerge 2.16.54.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 21:42:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html
</guid><description>
WinMerge is a tool to merge and distinguish open source for Windows. WinMerge can compare and folders and files, presenting differences in a visual text easy to understand or manipulate. WinMerge is very useful for determining what has changed between the version of the project and merge the changes between the versions. WinMerge can be used as a tool to compare / merge, external or as a standalone application.
In addition, Winmerge has many helpful features helps to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezPaycheck 3.16.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 21:39:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html
</guid><description>
ezPaycheck is a payroll software easy to use is designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. The developer of we have designed it to become a solution tax payroll internal for small businesses to calculate taxes, print paychecks for employees and contractors, generate reports and print tax forms.
The features of ezPaycheck
	Calculate payroll federal and state tax / deductions and local taxes (such as SDI tax, occupation tax, city)
	Print paychecks and tax...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezAccounting 3.16.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 21:38:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html
</guid><description>
ezAccounting is accounting software designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. ezAccounting is the solution internal accounting suitable for small businesses need to record and report on cash flow in and out including sales, incomes and expenses and purchases. It also supports payroll processing and print tax forms.
The features of ezAccounting
	Company accounts unlimited
	Custom format form
	Custom format Czech
	Support multiple tax code
	Support multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kindle for PC 2.8.70995</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 21:12:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html
</guid><description>
Kindle for PC is a handy and handy application that you can use to read a Kindle book with a computer without a Kindle device. To use it, you need to have an Amazon account registered, as the app will prompt you to log in as soon as the startup starts. Simple interface, which allows you to browse through your book library and manage your collections.
Features of Kindle for PC
	The navigation is so easy, because the entry can help you move to the desired chapter and you can use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.32</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:59:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.201</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:59:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:58:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.7 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:58:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Crawler PRO 1.1.21</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:57:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html
</guid><description>
Ensuring your website is properly indexed and has optimal SEO aspects can be more difficult than you think, but luckily, web crawlers like CrawlRhino SEO Crawler can professionally assist you. This application allows you to perform website crawls to analyze site structure, find broken links, duplicate entries, as well as perform in-depth SEO audits and generate reports that can be used to improve performance and resolve upcoming issues.
How CrawlRhino SEO Crawler Works
CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Sklad Plus 17.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:56:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-sklad-plus-3994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-sklad-plus-3994.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Sklad Plus is a warehouse management software easy to use. It helps you keep track of products and customers, simplifies the process of delivery, sales and invoicing and the management and control of warehouse / your store easier than ever. Vladovsoft Sklad Plus help you to easily export tables and reports as interactive web pages (in HTML format) and to XML. Automatically calculate the weighted average after product delivery. Preview, print, choose printer and print tables,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:56:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Monitor 1.0.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:55:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html
</guid><description>
CrawlRhino SEO Monitor is a professional desktop monitoring solution designed for digital agencies, SEO consultants, and businesses that depend on stable website performance.
It continuously tracks your site's uptime, downtime, and important SEO tag changes — including titles, meta descriptions, H1 headings, robots directives, and canonicals — so you can immediately identify any issues that could impact rankings or user experience.
Core Features of CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Fitorg 17.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:54:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-fitorg-5029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-fitorg-5029.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Fitorg is a software management room, easy to use, affordable. Vladovsoft Fitorg includes membership details, bookings, deliveries and sales, product, service, book, recipes, accounts, payments and track membership. Ideal for fitness clubs, gym, health club, entertainment center, and fitness.
The advantages of Vladovsoft Fitorg
	The software is optimized for fast operation even on the computer and old laptop
	Management software, club very easy to use
	User...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.41.103683.2151</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:53:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download POPcon PRO 4.9.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 20:53:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-popcon-pro-14560.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-popcon-pro-14560.html
</guid><description>
POPcon PRO connects your MS Exchange server to POP3 and IMAP mailboxes. It includes all the features of the POPcon Standard version plus antivirus, anti-spam, and rule-based delivery functionality. POPcon PRO downloads emails from POP3, POP3-SSL, IMAP, and IMAP-SSL mailboxes and distributes them to Exchange or Domino mailboxes based on recipient information found in the email header.
The software runs as a background service on any Windows Server version compatible with .NET 4.7.2...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:06:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download NanaZip 6.0.1638.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:05:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html
</guid><description>
NanaZip is an open source file archiver for the modern Windows experience, forked from the source code of the popular open source file archiver 7-Zip. NanaZip is considered an interesting alternative to WinRAR and WinZip. According to tests, NanaZip provides about 10% better compression ratio than WinRAR and WinZip.
Supported formats:
	Packing/unpacking: 7Z, ZIP, XZ, BZIP2, GZIP, TAR and WIM.
	Extract: RAR, AR, ARJ, CAB, CHM, CPIO, CramFS, DMG, EXT, FAT, GPT, HFS, IHEX, ISO, LZH,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Commander 19.0.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:04:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Commander software brings user photo management tool effectively cover view, sort, edit, convert photos and images to the web. Ashampoo Photo Commander 16 will surprise you immediately! Interface modern user will quickly learn the features of your favorite and adjust accordingly for faster access. The slideshow images appear in the mode 4K stunning and the panoramic feature will steals the show.
Ashampoo Photo Commander - photo editing
Software Ashampoo Photo Commander...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 242.4.5815</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:04:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:03:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 128.0.5807.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:02:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:01:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.377/149</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:00:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2602)</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:59:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 18.13 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:58:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item></channel></rss>