<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 19:54:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 19:54:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:27:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniGetUI 3.3.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:27:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html
</guid><description>
UniGetUI (formerly WingetUI) is a graphical user interface for WinGet (and other package managers), a command-line package manager for Windows 10 and Windows 11 such as Winget, Scoop, Chocolatey, Pip, NPM, .NET Tool and PowerShell Gallery. It allows users to install, update and uninstall software from the package manager easily. Additionally, it provides features like backup, restore, group and update your packages and receive notifications about new updates.
With this program, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:25:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.4.8.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:23:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanoramaStudio Pro 4.1.6.445</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:22:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html
</guid><description>
PanoramaStudio Pro is software is the complete solution for creating panoramic images as matching images are arranged arbitrary in the panorama. PanoramaStudio Pro creates panoramic images in a row and multiple rows of up to 360x180 spherical full. In addition, this software provides viewer / player application HTML5 interactions are compatible with all web browsers and on multiple systems to display the panoramic image 3D, 360 degree images and image zoom on the site.
PanoramaStudio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.30.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:16:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ViewCompanion Premium 16.22.0.1116</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:15:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viewcompanion-premium-1868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viewcompanion-premium-1868.html
</guid><description>
ViewCompanion Premium version is the most powerful in all versions of ViewCompmate. ViewCompanion Premium can view, print and convert the file plot PLT, Adobe PDF, Autodesk DWF, Postcript, CGM, TIFF, CALS and other formats. ViewCompanion premium files, support PLT plotter using HPGL, HPGL / 2, HP-RTL, and formats Calcomp.
ViewCompanion Premium
With ViewCompanion Premium, you can add bookmarks to files has download. The markup elements are supported, including rectangles, lines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Convert Ultimate 25.10.1692</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:15:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html
</guid><description>
Full Convert Enterprise is a conversion software database. Full Convert Enterprise create all the tables, copy all of your data. Full Convert Enterprise has the custom features and mapped powerful at your disposal, your data will be moved out of the box without custom. Full Convert automatically adjusted the basis of your data and use copy modes optimized for each separate table to achieve information best possible quality.
Full Convert Enterprise - convert data base
Full Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.6.3.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:14:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD 2026.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk AutoCAD design software is computer-aided (CAD) which the architects, engineers and construction professionals rely on to create the 2D and 3D drawings accurately. Autodesk AutoCAD will allow you to design and shape the world around you using the powerful features and flexibility of it. Speed documentation, share ideas seamlessly, and explore ideas more intuitively in 3D. With thousands of add-ons available, AutoCAD offers maximum flexibility, is customized for the specific needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.52</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:13:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD LT 2026.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:13:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html
</guid><description>
AutoCAD LT 2024 is designed for the development and detailing of 2D drawings. The program automates most of the phases of the project. A complete set of 2D commands allows you to create drawings, modify them, and publish working documents for projects. can easily transfer files to other professionals. Additionally, you can customize the program's user interface to fit your needs.
Features of AutoCAD LT
	Create and edit 2D drawings.
	Annotate drawings with text, dimensions, paths, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.18.0.8 + Professional</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:12:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.0.1015 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:11:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:10:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ekahau AI Pro 11.8.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:09:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekahau-ai-pro-7947.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekahau-ai-pro-7947.html
</guid><description>
Ekahau AI Pro is powerful Wi-Fi planning software and AI design for the most reliable, best performing wireless networks, now including 6GHz. Ekahau AI Pro is the Wi-Fi design software top choice for IT professionals for business-critical Wi-Fi design and implementation projects.
Use the new Channel Planner and Network Simulator to show recommended improvements to your existing network design, or start a redesign with the complete AI Automated Planner completely new and discover optimal...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:09:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 11.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:02:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Document Reader and Viewer 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:37:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html
</guid><description>
All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents is a smart office application that helps you read all documents downloaded from the internet, supports reading PDF files, PDF Reader, doc, docx xls, ppt, txt, excel, xlxs files... fast, easy and convenient.. All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents are providing multiple Document reading features including PDF Reader, Docs Reader &amp;amp; Docx, ppt reader, xls reader, txt, excel &amp;amp; documents different from readers.
All Document...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.8.1 build 2510282</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:37:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.54.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:36:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Tools 2 v1.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:36:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html
</guid><description>
Smart Tools is a complete package of 6 individual applications. It has 6 sets below with a total of 15 tools.
	Offline support (Wi-Fi tablets only): Open this section multiple times using internet, you can open it without internet.
	Magnetic sensor required. So this app cannot support some Android devices (e.g. HTC One V).
	This is one of the essential applications of Google Play for Education.
6 application sets include:
	Set 1. Smart Ruler Pro: length, angle, slope, level,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.90</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:36:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item></channel></rss>