<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 17:45:26 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 17:45:26 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF Viewer Pro 2025.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:14:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html
</guid><description>
Whether you're working alone or collaborating with a team, PDF Viewer Pro maximizes productivity, allowing you to view, search, and annotate PDF documents easily on your phone or tablet. your Android tablet or Chromebook.
Features of PDF Viewer Pro
View documents on the go
	Easily open PDF files from your favorite cloud provider, email, or directly from the website you're browsing.
	Search for the exact text you are looking for in the document.
	Double-tap the screen to Smart Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 15.7.57128</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:14:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner – Phone Cleaner 25.15.0 build 800011217</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:13:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner is a system cleaning and optimization tool for Android devices. CCleaner for Android allows users to delete unnecessary files, such as temporary files and caches, as well as identify and uninstall applications that are taking up too much space on the device. It also includes a task kill to close running applications and free up memory. This can help free up storage space and improve device performance. In addition, CCleaner for Android also has a security feature that allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voice Recorder Plus: Rec Sound 1.13.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:13:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html
</guid><description>
Unlock the full potential of your recordings with Sound Recorder Plus &amp;amp; Dictaphone, your solution for perfect audio quality at your fingertips. Designed with a beautiful, intuitive interface, this app is suitable for both beginners and seasoned professionals. Whether it is for working, studying, listening to music or recording the essence of everyday life, Audio Recorder Free is the embodiment of high-quality and flexible audio recording or voice recording.
Key features of Voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:12:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.3.2-2452</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:12:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Translate Voice Translator 423.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:11:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talkao-translate-translator-8426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talkao-translate-translator-8426.html
</guid><description>
You can hold a conversation in any language with the help of a voice translator, translate different texts and use the button app to chat. Learn languages ​​quickly and easily, speak your language to translate written or spoken words in the language of your choice, more than 80 languages ​​in text such as English Spanish, French, German, Italian, Korean, Chinese, Japanese and 44 languages ​​spoken such as those mentioned above and many more such as Arabic, Danish, Dutch,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.3.0-250724</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:11:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Projectivy Launcher 4.66</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:11:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-projectivy-launcher-8369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-projectivy-launcher-8369.html
</guid><description>
Projectivy Launcher is an alternative launcher for Android TV, designed specifically for your TV and projector needs: smooth, clean, customizable and packed with unique features. It's Projectivy Tools on steroids.
Projectivy Launcher Features
	No ads
	Shortcut to change input source (HDMI 1/2/3, AV) and on-screen menu popup
	Autostart directly with any external input or installed application
	Parental controls to prevent HDMI/app use during certain times of day
	Detect inactivity to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mock Locations (fake GPS path) 1.35.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:10:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mock-locations-fake-gps-path-10782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mock-locations-fake-gps-path-10782.html
</guid><description>
Mock Locations allows you to fake information about your phone's location according to GPS and network operator. You just need to navigate the route on the map and press the "Go!" there are apps all over your phone that provide fake location information. This will help with application development or if you don't want anyone to know where you really are.
Simulated Location Features
	Simulated GPS location and according to service provider.
	Ability to create routes on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download RoughAnimator - animation app 4.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:10:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-roughanimator-animation-app-9365.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-roughanimator-animation-app-9365.html
</guid><description>
RoughAnimator is a full-featured hand-drawn animation app for Android. Made by an animator, for animators. Powerful enough for experts, simple enough for beginners. Everything you need to create traditional frame-by-frame hand-drawn animations everywhere you go!
Features of RoughAnimator - animation app
	Timeline with unlimited layers and easily adjustable exposure length of each drawing, for animating poses or straight transitions
	Peel the onion
	Playback preview
	Scrub over...
</description></item><item><title>Download aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks 2.9.2 build 2009200</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:10:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html
</guid><description>
aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks is a popular calendar and task manager app for Android devices. It is developed by Tapir Apps GmbH and acts as an enhanced version of the free aCalendar app. aCalendar+ offers a variety of features and customization options to help users stay organized and manage their schedules and tasks effectively.
Features of aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks Tasks
	intuitive navigation with smooth transitions
	day, week, month and year views
	full screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download ISS Detector Pro 2.05.42</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:09:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-detector-pro-8393.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-detector-pro-8393.html
</guid><description>
You can actually see it in the night sky. View Starlink satellite ships with Famous Objects (available in the Filter menu). If you like space or astronomy, you will love this ISS tracking app. ISS Detector Pro includes the functionality of ISS Detector (free) with all Extensions and no ads.
ISS Detector Pro will tell you when and where to look for the International Space Station or Iridium flares. You get a warning a few minutes before passing. You'll never miss a pass by the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Video Camera [High Quality] 8.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:09:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-video-camera-10568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-video-camera-10568.html
</guid><description>
This is the best silent video camera. You can record videos without worrying about the shutter sound even in public spaces. It is very useful for recording videos for sleeping baby or playing pets, etc.
The silent video camera can record Full HD (1920x1080) movies, so it is very clear to your memories.
Silent video camera features
	Full HD (1920x1080) Movie recording
	Still photo capture
	Flashlight for recording in dark environment
	Support zoom control and exposure control
Silent...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnet Search - Torrent Search 1.2.97</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:08:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnet-search-pro-torrent-tool-10821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnet-search-pro-torrent-tool-10821.html
</guid><description>
You can use this app to search for the resource you want, then copy the magnet link and download it. That's easy. You can also search for torrents, have a good time.
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Cleanup – Phone Cleaner 25.15.0 build 800011217</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:03:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html
</guid><description>
Avast Cleanup - Phone Cleaner is a mobile app for Android devices designed to help users optimize their phone's performance and free up storage space. This application provides many tools and features to clean and speed up your phone.
One of the main features of Avast Cleanup is the Junk Cleaner, which scans your phone for unnecessary files such as temporary files, app cache, and other junk data. The app will then provide a list of files that can be safely deleted to free up space on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resize Me! Pro - Photo resizer 2.5.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:03:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-resize-me-pro-photo-resizer-12970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-resize-me-pro-photo-resizer-12970.html
</guid><description>
Resize Me! Pro - Photo resizer is an Android application developed by XnView, allowing users to easily resize photos before sharing on social networking platforms such as Twitter, Facebook and Instagram or sending via email.
Features of Resize Me!
	Customize size
	Easy to use use
	Keep EXIF ​​tags
	Keep GPS data
	Rotate and crop
	Save as JPEG or PNG format
	Set as wallpaper
	Share or save results
</description></item><item><title>Download IELTS® Vocabulary Flashcards 2.0 build 21</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:03:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-vocabulary-flashcards-10183.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-vocabulary-flashcards-10183.html
</guid><description>
The International English Language Testing System (IELTS) has become the world's most popular English test for study, work and migration. IELTS Vocabulary Flashcards is an app that covers the most important words used for the real IELTS test and helps you achieve your goals.
The words are intelligently extracted by their repetition and importance in 52 tests from Cambridge exams. Cambridge Tests is a comprehensive set of practice IELTS tests (13 books are covered and each book contains...
</description></item><item><title>Download CALCU Stylish Basic Calculator 4.7.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html
</guid><description>
Express your style with a computer made just for you. Choose a stylish, colorful theme to brighten your day while you calculate with ease. CALCU™ is easy to use for everyday calculations, with all the scientific capabilities you need for work and school at a swipe. And for your most demanding needs, CALCU™ lets you add or remove the functions and constants you need to create the perfect calculator you designed for you.
Features of Fashion Calculator - CALCU
	Try our new Material...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.41.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:01:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download DNS Changer Fast &amp;amp;amp; Secure Surf 1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dns-changer-fast-secure-surf-11428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dns-changer-fast-secure-surf-11428.html
</guid><description>
DNS Changer Android is the first layer of internet security that provides essential protection against surveillance and censorship efforts. With just one tap, the app will find the fastest DNS server and connect to it to improve your network connection. It is the easiest way to change your DNS and test DNS server speed. Smart app works without root for both WiFi and mobile network data connections. You can choose from the list of available DNS or change it to your custom DNS.
Using DNS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector - Spyware 6.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:57:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html
</guid><description>
Anti-spy scanner &amp;amp; Spyware is an Android app that scans your device for spyware and other harmful applications that can compromise your privacy and security. This is a useful tool for users who want to ensure their devices are not infected with spyware or other malware that could collect sensitive information or cause other harm.
Anti Spy has been developed to scan Android devices to detect potential spies effectively. Thanks to artificial intelligence (AI), real-time signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reminder Pro 4.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:56:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a simple pop-up reminder app? Do you want to create reminders for one-time and recurring tasks? Get reminders and increase your productivity. Never forget an important task again! Finally, a simple and easy way to set reminders or deadline notifications. This hourly reminder app gets straight to the point. Set notifications to remind you of all your tasks, chores, and to-do list items, then sit back and clear your head.
No unnecessary or complicated features....
</description></item><item><title>Download CalcKit: All-In-One Calculator 7.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:52:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calckit-all-in-one-calculator-8514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calckit-all-in-one-calculator-8514.html
</guid><description>
CalcKit is a multifunctional calculator application for mobile devices. It provides a convenient and flexible way to perform mathematical calculations on your phone or tablet. Designed with simplicity in mind, CalcKit helps you solve all kinds of everyday calculations. From simple and complex calculations to unit and currency conversions, percentages, areas, volumes, etc.
Passionate development combined with continuous feedback from users has created what we believe is the best...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microphone Blocker &amp;amp; Guard 6.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:52:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-microphone-blocker-guard-8478.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-microphone-blocker-guard-8478.html
</guid><description>
Microphone Blocker &amp;amp; Guard ensures that no hacker or spy can eavesdrop on you. With just one click, your Android device's built-in microphone will be fully protected. With just one click, protection is activated, and Micro Guard blocks and observes all programs and processes that try to access your smartphone's microphone. Any attempt to breach security will be reported by signal.
Block the microphone, protect recording, mute the microphone, and protect yourself from microphone...
</description></item></channel></rss>