<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:47:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:47:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 037</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus 8.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:45:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-8135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-8135.html
</guid><description>
Calculator Plus is a perfect calculator program for Android that is easy to read and saves you time and effort. It can remember everything you calculate and let you review it at any time, making it perfect for shopping, doing homework, balancing a checkbook, or even helping with taxes. .
Plus Calculator Features
	Calculator Plus displays your calculations in clear, elegant, easy-to-read typeface, with commas in the right places
	You'll never forget where you are in the calculation - I...
</description></item><item><title>Download Star Tracker - Mobile Sky Map 1.6.112</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:45:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-star-tracker-mobile-sky-map-8470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-star-tracker-mobile-sky-map-8470.html
</guid><description>
Go out with your friends and enjoy stargazing! Let StarTracker guide you through the universe. Just hold your device up and point it at the sky and have fun! You can see any stars, constellations, and deep sky objects you are observing in real time.
This is an astronomy app for Android devices that allows users to identify stars, planets, and other celestial objects in the night sky. The app uses your device's built-in GPS, accelerometer and compass to accurately display the current sky...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rain Alarm 6.0.0 build 700</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:45:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html
</guid><description>
This weather app alerts you when rain is approaching. Alerts are a reliable short-term forecast based on near real-time data. This app is more accurate and reliable than a traditional forecast. It is useful for all outdoor activities - including cycling, motorcycling, hiking, gardening, BBQs, picnics, dog walking and DIY.
Features of Rain Alarm for Android
	Alerts for all types of precipitation, whether rain, snow or hail
	Alerts as a notification with vibration and/or sound
	Simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download EOBD Facile: OBD2 Car Scanner 3.77.1113</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:44:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html
</guid><description>
Run diagnostics on your car with your Android Smartphone or tablet and discover why the engine light is on... no need to check the manufacturer's manual! Connect the ELM 327 interface to your car's OBD2 port and run the app: you will be able to read engine and transmission error codes and view data from your vehicle in real time.
EOBD Facile features for Android
	View engine and transmission fault codes (also known as DTCs) and see what they mean (over 11,000 definitions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Icon Pack Studio 2.3 build 003 GP</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:44:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-icon-pack-studio-11209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-icon-pack-studio-11209.html
</guid><description>
IPS was created with the idea that no icon pack can fit your home screen better than an icon pack you create yourself. With IPS, you can create an icon pack from scratch, or you can download and apply one of the thousands of icons uploaded by our community every day. The advanced editor allows you to resize and move any element in your custom icon. Use special filters like lights, shadows, textures and borders, and when you're satisfied with the results, apply the new icon pack to your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Layer - Photo Editor 2.22.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:44:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-layer-photo-editor-10558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-layer-photo-editor-10558.html
</guid><description>
Multi Layer is a full-featured photo editor that can edit and arrange images into multiple layers. It supports selection tools (manual and magic wand tools) to selectively edit brightness, contrast, saturation, hue, and RGB color levels.
This app can perform any photo editing action: edit each layer independently, stack layers, blend modes, remove background with transparency, magic wand to choose and edit eye color, red eye, whiten,..., create amazing effects like flipping and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.5.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:43:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation | Gotta Yoga 2.1.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:43:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html
</guid><description>
Gotta Yoga is a versatile yoga and meditation app designed for users of all levels, from beginners to advanced practitioners. The app offers over 350 classes, including styles like Vinyasa, Yin, Hatha, Ashtanga, Iyengar, meditation and pranayama, with session lengths ranging from 5 to 90 minutes, many of which can be taken offline.
Key features include:
	Live classes via Zoom with certified yoga teachers, providing real-time interaction and feedback.
	Integrated with Apple Health and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeakFinder 4.8.49</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:43:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html
</guid><description>
Explore more mountains than any other climber! PeakFinder AR makes it possible… and shows the names of all the mountains and peaks with a 360° panoramic display. This functionality is completely offline - and worldwide! PeakFinder knows more than 650,000 mountain peaks - from Mount Everest to that little hill on the corner.
PeakFinder Features
	Works offline and worldwide
	Includes more than 650,000 peak names
	Install the camera image using a panoramic drawing *
	Display real-time...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fing - Network Tools 12.10.3 build 121003000</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:42:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html
</guid><description>
Fing is a popular network scanning application that allows users to discover devices connected to the local network, view their IP and MAC addresses, and perform various network tests. Fing is the #1 Network Scanner: detects all devices connected to your WiFi and identifies them with our patented technology that is also used by router manufacturers and companies antivirus used worldwide.
Features of Fing for Android
	Network Scan: Quickly find all devices connected to your Wi-Fi...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyRadar Weather Radar Premium 8.63.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:38:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myradar-weather-radar-8127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myradar-weather-radar-8127.html
</guid><description>
MyRadar is a weather monitoring and forecasting application for Android devices. It provides users with real-time weather information, including radar maps, current conditions, and forecasts for locations around the world. To use MyRadar, users must download the app from the Google Play Store or other Android app store or taiwebs.com.
Features of MyRadar Weather Radar Pro APK
	Animated radar map shows the movement of precipitation over time
	Current temperature, humidity, and wind...
</description></item><item><title>Download Background Video Recorder Pro 13.3.75</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:37:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-video-recorder-pro-10919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-video-recorder-pro-10919.html
</guid><description>
This application helps you record videos in the background even when the screen is closed. it has many other useful features, such as: remote camera control with Wear OS, motion detector with artificial intelligence algorithm, baby monitoring, calendar recording and continuous photo capture.
You can also control the camera with the volume button or 1 of 3 supported widgets
	"Big red button" - record video.
	"Big green button" - motion detection.
	"Big orange button" - takes photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ventusky: Weather Maps &amp;amp; Radar 47.0 build 47002</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:37:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ventusky-weather-maps-radar-8682.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ventusky-weather-maps-radar-8682.html
</guid><description>
This app combines extremely accurate weather forecasts for your location with a map that shows the weather in a much larger area in a very interesting way. This allows you to see where the rain will come from or where the wind is blowing. What makes this app unique is the amount of data it displays. Weather forecasts, precipitation, wind, cloud cover, atmospheric pressure, snow cover and other meteorological data for different altitudes are available worldwide.
The maps are interactive,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chronus Information Widgets 25.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:36:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chronus-information-widgets-11120.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chronus-information-widgets-11120.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to Chronus, a versatile and stylish set of Clock, Weather, News, Tasks, Stocks and Calendar widgets for your Home and Lock screens. All Chronus widgets share the same highly optimized backend services, making it the perfect, single replacement for many other standalone widgets on your device. This ensures your system will use less CPU, data, and battery while still providing you with rich information.
Chronus Information Widget Features
	Fully functional Flex, Flex (Analog),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Radio Player - TuneFm 1.10.57</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-internet-radio-player-tunefm-13412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-internet-radio-player-tunefm-13412.html
</guid><description>
TuneFM - Radio Player is the best way to listen to radio stations from all over the world! There are more than 7 thousand radio stations. The application offers a very simple and intuitive interface. TuneFM is Chromecast ready.
Key Features
	Listen to all-time favorites.
	Bookmark stations for instant access.
	Discover new music and save to Spotify.
	Sleep well with our sleep timer.
	Add unique radio stations to our growing list.
	Personalize with color themes.
	️ Seamless...
</description></item><item><title>Download Call Filter 1.24.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:33:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-call-filter-12022.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-call-filter-12022.html
</guid><description>
Call Filter is a simple and effective application to block unwanted calls. This app is free, contains no ads, and does not collect or transfer personal and contact data.
Unlike other blocking apps, Call Filter does not require access to your contacts. It is easy to use and stable in operation.
Blocked number database is updated several times a day. Your phone automatically selects the refresh rate based on battery status, Internet connection speed, and connection type (Wi-Fi, LTE, H+,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7-Zip 25.01</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:25:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-446.html
</guid><description>
7Zip is a file storage and open source, provide high compression rate, the most used format f new 7z, bringing compression results are better than 30-50% compared with the ZIP standard. We have tested it with a log file, server is compressed with ZIP had a file size of 18 mb and using 7-Zip was reduced to 8 mb (results may vary, depending on the file type).
In addition, 7Zip also supports the formats 7z, ZIP, CAB, RAR, ARJ, GZIP, BZIP2, TAR, CPIO, RPM and DEB, so it can also be used...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAR - Disk ARchive 2.8.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:20:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dar-disk-archive-9009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dar-disk-archive-9009.html
</guid><description>
DAR is a command line backup and archiving tool that uses selective compression (does not compress compressed files), strong encryption, can split archives into different files of certain size and provide fast hashing, supporting differential backups with or without delta , ftp and sftp binaries for remote cloud storage.
Internal storage directory, allowing very fast recovery of even a single file from a huge archive, finally trimmed, compressed, encrypted finally placed on a cloud...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.13.5291</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:18:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2025 v12.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:17:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:17:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:15:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for OFX 2025 v12.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:15:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro for OFX is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro for OFX is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro for OFX 2020
New features in version...
</description></item><item><title>Download DNSQuerySniffer 1.97</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:14:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dnsquerysniffer-1762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dnsquerysniffer-1762.html
</guid><description>
DNSQuerySniffer is a network utility to track all DNS queries are sent from your system in real-time and reports them in a list can sort, along with the port number, IP address, request type, response code and other details. With DNSQuerySniffer you can sort the report by column header, and optionally export the selected items to HTML reports.
DNSQuerySniffer - Monitor DNS queries
DNSQuerySniffer does not require installation, meaning that it can carry is and you just drop the EXE file...
</description></item></channel></rss>