<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:38:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:38:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:34:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClassicMenu by Reuschtools 4.70</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:34:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicmenu-by-reuschtools-13987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicmenu-by-reuschtools-13987.html
</guid><description>
ClassicMenu by Reuschtools is a software tool designed for Windows that allows users to switch between the classic and the new context menu introduced in Windows 11. The tool allows the classic context menu to be enabled or disabled, which is useful for users who prefer the traditional full context menu over the newer compact version with fewer items. ClassicMenu is free, requires no installation (click to run), and is accessible from the Start Menu after installing Reuschtools.
When...
</description></item><item><title>Download Iperius Backup Full 8.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:30:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html
</guid><description>
Iperius Backup software supports backup and restore of data can be stored on a cloud service, and AES 256-bit. This is the perfect software to get the advantages of the many services that cloud storage is provided by the famous supplier like Google or Microsoft. With a single application, you will can easily save your files externally on Google Drive, Dropbox or Microsoft SkyDrive.
Iperius Backup uses the technology images Windows drive most advanced, allows to copy entire operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.102.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Craft Director Studio v25.2.1 for 3DS Max &amp;amp; Maya 2018-2026</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:28:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-craft-director-studio-4360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-craft-director-studio-4360.html
</guid><description>
Craft Director Studio - this Solution extends creative possibilities by eliminating the time consuming task of creating key frames, scripts. Users get experience of the era of the new cartoon with the opportunity to create the natural movement while moving, arbitrary use input device, gaining instant gratification through animated, real-time interactive reality.
Craft Director Studio - Create animations of vehicles
With the plug-in to add this animation, you just need to connect with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Roxio Easy CD &amp;amp; DVD Burning 2 v20.0.125.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:27:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-easy-cd-dvd-burning-8018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-easy-cd-dvd-burning-8018.html
</guid><description>
Roxio Easy CD &amp;amp; DVD Burning v2 is an industry-leading toolkit to burn and rip CD and DVD with just a few easy clicks. Simply drag and drop priceless music, photos, and video files from your desktop to disc. Save music, video backups, and other large files on multiple discs. Create your perfect music playlist or create custom CD with personalized disc labels and fades. Turn your old cassettes into digital files, eliminating pop-ups and clicks. Enhance and preserve your photos with...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:27:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Roxio Creator NXT Pro 9 v22.1.236.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:26:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-creator-nxt-pro-8906.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-creator-nxt-pro-8906.html
</guid><description>
Roxio Creator NXT Pro is a software suite for Windows computers that provides a variety of multimedia tools for editing, recording, and sharing digital media content. It is designed to be an all-in-one solution for managing photos, videos, music and other media files.
Combining more than 25 Roxio products into one, Roxio Creator NXT Pro 9 can fulfill all your creative and digital needs. Record your screen and record video from multiple cameras. The software includes various...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.2.0.2961</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:26:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download WildBit Viewer Pro 6.18 Commercial</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:25:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wildbit-viewer-pro-1694.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wildbit-viewer-pro-1694.html
</guid><description>
WildBit Viewer is compact photo viewer and quick with slideshow and editor. Look in the folder fast, the file list and the thumbnail view. Viewer includes also image info with meta data EXIF support for JPEG and TIFF information and IPTC (IIMV4) (such as information file PhotoShop) from JPEG and TIFF, Thumbview can change the view mode, sorting and thumbnail size is predefined to set thumbnail size quickly.
WildBit Viewer Pro
WildBit Viewer also includes a toolbar shell, you can drop...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1060</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1060</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:24:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPIM Business 18.70.5901</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:24:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpim-business-4685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpim-business-4685.html
</guid><description>
WinPIM Business is a program that helps you manage the conversations, the online meetings. WinPIM Business help you arrange your time effectively by allowing you to create a contact list with details of everyone you need. You can add name, company and telephone number of their ease.
The features of WinPIM Business
	Storage more than 60 fields and 20 custom fields.
	Create Tree Tree to manage contacts, and can map contacts.
	Quick phone dial, mail, fax, visit the website.
	Remind...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.16.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:19:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download KJ File Manager 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:19:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html
</guid><description>
KJ File Manager is a program that will allow you to easily manage the audio and video files in karaoke format, you can now record MP3 tags ID and edit metadata information, done all in batch mode.
Easily manage files karaoke, video and audio of you and fixes title easily with batch editing powerful. Support the format name standard most popular. Automatic fix for underscores and capitalization, swap title and artist, shift, split, and replace field data on multiple files at once,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoResizerOK 3.44</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:32:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoresizerok-6303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoresizerok-6303.html
</guid><description>
PhotoResizerOK is a tool that allows you to quickly reduce your file size to not release your original image on social platforms! After converting the files, you can select the folder where you want to save them. You can also drag and drop them directly from the list to the Windows Explorer directory.
Even if you start, you can start immediately without having to face the complex knowledge of photos and photos! But it ' s also good for professional photographers who want to quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPing 2.77</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:32:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winping-4525.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winping-4525.html
</guid><description>
WinPing is a compact application that helps you check the speed your computer sends and receives data packages from websites or local computer. The application allows you to configure a few rules in order to have accurate results. The options Menu allows you to select elements will be displayed, sets the timeout in milliseconds for multiplication and the amount of time or even the activation process infinite loop, with the ability to enter the loop, customized to run before...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.6.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:31:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download FakeDriveCheck 4.70</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:31:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html
</guid><description>
FakeDriveCheck is a simple utility you can run to verify if your USB stick or MicroSD card is fake. It's easy to get and use, making it a good choice for anyone skeptical about the authenticity of their external storage.
FakeDriveCheck Features
	Existing files will not be destroyed while the USB drive is verified.
	Super fast verification.
	No need to unplug and plug in.
	Hot Plug: FakeDriveCheck detects USB drives
	inserted after FakeDriveCheck is started.
</description></item><item><title>Download Reuschtools CopyMob 4.70</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:30:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copymob-14146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copymob-14146.html
</guid><description>
CopyMob allows you to seamlessly copy photos and music between your smartphone and PC. This feature allows for easy access and management of multimedia content across multiple devices. Its core functionality revolves around the seamless transfer of image and audio files through a user-friendly multi-step process that is suitable for both novice and experienced users.
To create a stable connection, CopyMob uses a USB interface, ensuring stable and fast data transfer. Once the connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 15.9.57971</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Super File Manager Explorer 1.5.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:28:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-esuper-file-explorer-9196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-esuper-file-explorer-9196.html
</guid><description>
ESuper File Explorer is a file management app for Android devices that allows users to browse and manage files on their devices. Free, safe and simple, manage your files efficiently and easily with ESuper File Explorer. ESuper File Explorer is a simple and powerful file explorer for Android devices. It's free, fast and fully functional.
Features of ESuper File Explorer
	Shortcut bar: Supports all file operations
	Cleaner: Clean all junk files with just one click
	Disk analysis:...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.10.267399</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:28:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Utilities 8.3.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:28:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-utilities-8758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-utilities-8758.html
</guid><description>
Network Utilities is an Android application that provides users with a set of tools to analyze and manage their network connections. It is a useful tool for users who want to troubleshoot network problems, monitor network activity, and optimize network performance. It is also available for purchase with additional features such as ad-free browsing, more advanced network tools, and more detailed network analysis.
The following tools are currently available: 
	Network Info will display...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPS Speedometer : Odometer HUD 15.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:28:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-speedometer-odometer-hud-13950.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-speedometer-odometer-hud-13950.html
</guid><description>
Discover the ideal companion for your driver with this Speedometer and Odometer app – an all-in-one GPS speed tracker and trip meter. Whether you're driving, cycling, racing, or simply curious about your speed, this app provides accurate speed measurements right at your fingertips.
This app is a perfect temporary replacement for your broken speedometer. You will definitely benefit from this speedometer app in one way or another.
Key Features
	Real-Time Speed Tracking: Track your...
</description></item></channel></rss>