<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:31:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:31:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:27:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.44</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:26:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.4.200</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:25:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Safety Scanner 1.435.364.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:25:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Safety Scanner is a scanning tool designed to find and remove malware from a Windows computer. Just download and run the scan to find malware and try to reverse the changes made by the threat identified. Microsoft Safety Scanner has the ability to remove virus, spyware and files other dangers on your computer, Microsoft Safety Scanner completes scanning tasks in just a few minutes, while the computer is moderate stress during handling.
In other words, no real time protection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.4.200</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:24:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiBit Uninstaller 3.2.70 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:23:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hibit-uninstaller-3897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hibit-uninstaller-3897.html
</guid><description>
HiBit Uninstaller offer alternative solution for applet "Programs and features" standard of Windows allows you to uninstall software.
Software HiBit Uninstaller offer you a list of all the programs currently installed and allows you to uninstall any item that does not leave any rest whatsoever. HiBit Uninstaller will first launch the application uninstall comes standard with software and after removal is complete, it will provide you scan every file, directory and registry entries left by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows USB Blocker 6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:23:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-usb-blocker-10286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-usb-blocker-10286.html
</guid><description>
Windows USB Blocker is a useful tool to quickly Block or unblock USB Storage Devices on any Windows system. USB devices are one of the main reasons why viruses/malware spread from one system to another without the user's knowledge. It is often very dangerous to allow someone else to insert a USB (often infected with a virus) into your system. Therefore, we always recommend that you turn off USB when not in use.
In such cases, Windows USB Blocker tool will help you block USB immediately...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Safely Remove 7.1.2.1328</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 17:03:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-safely-remove-122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-safely-remove-122.html
</guid><description>
USB Safely Remove is a great program to automate work with devices your mobile. For example, you can easily specify the launch the program you need when disconnecting or connecting equipment, plus you have access to the command line, you can download USB Safely Remove in the full news. I would like to note an interesting feature of the program is that you can stop the USB device by pressing the hot key and the unique technology of the program will allow you to know why the device you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo AI Pro 4.0.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 17:02:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download RealVNC VNC Server Enterprise 7.15.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 17:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vnc-connect-enterprise-2057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vnc-connect-enterprise-2057.html
</guid><description>
VNC Connect Enterprise is the management software but update keeps you connected with remote access to another computer for control in real time anywhere in the world. VNC Connect Enterprise technology use VNC to connect, this is the latest version (6+) of software, remote access, multi-platform our for personal purposes and commercial.
VNC Connect, Enterprise - connect remote access
The features of VNC Connect Enterprise
A product for all needs remote access to your
	VNC Connect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 17:01:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:57:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2025 v212</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:56:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download hashcat 7.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:56:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashcat-6759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashcat-6759.html
</guid><description>
hashcat is the world's fastest and most advanced password recovery utility, supporting five unique attack modes for over 300 highly-optimized hashing algorithms. hashcat currently supports CPUs, GPUs, and other hardware accelerators on Linux, Windows, and macOS and has facilities to help enable distributed password cracking.
Features of hashcat
	Open-Source (MIT License)
	Multi-OS (Linux, Windows, and macOS)
	Multi-Platform (CPU, GPU, APU, etc., everything that comes with an OpenCL...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v234</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:50:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download TapinRadio Pro 2.16.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:45:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapinradio-pro-735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapinradio-pro-735.html
</guid><description>
TapinRadio Pro is a professional software used to listen to the radio there are many channels to choose from and continuously updated. TapinRadio supports most of the formats internet radio - mp3, wma, ogg, aac. This is a powerful tool for you to capture information in the world and in country in the fastest and simplest.
TapinRadio Pro - Listen To The Radio
Features of TapinRadio Pro
	A lot of stations to choose from
	Supports most of the formats internet radio - mp3, wma, vorbis...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Plan 3D Tape Measure, Ruler 4.10.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:44:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-plan-3d-tape-measure-ruler-8786.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-plan-3d-tape-measure-ruler-8786.html
</guid><description>
AR Floorplan 3D – Innovative measurement application, augmented reality (AR, lidar scanner) for quick room measurement. AR camera sensor technology allows placing virtual tape measure on real surface, making the process of measuring and creating 3D floor plan much easier and faster. Using the device's camera sensor - sketch a house, draw a blueprint, build a design.
With the AR Plan 3D ruler app, you can
	Measure the perimeter and height of a room in Metric or Imperial units (cm, m,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DNS Changer Fast &amp;amp;amp; Secure Surf 1.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:44:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dns-changer-fast-secure-surf-11428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dns-changer-fast-secure-surf-11428.html
</guid><description>
DNS Changer Android is the first layer of internet security that provides essential protection against surveillance and censorship efforts. With just one tap, the app will find the fastest DNS server and connect to it to improve your network connection. It is the easiest way to change your DNS and test DNS server speed. Smart app works without root for both WiFi and mobile network data connections. You can choose from the list of available DNS or change it to your custom DNS.
Using DNS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Toolmaps 5.65</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:43:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-toolmaps-12981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-toolmaps-12981.html
</guid><description>
Toolmaps for Google Maps to highlight, edit and capture maps from Google Maps. Maps from Google Maps are displayed in full screen or immersive mode without any intervening objects.
	You can add and edit polylines, polygons, rectangles, circles and markers.
	You can also add colored text, resize and rotate them
	All colors support transparency.
Other features
	calculate perimeter and area of ​​polygons
	calculate distance between two points
	import / export to kml format
	easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal TV Remote Control 1.7.1 build 58</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-universal-tv-remote-control-9202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-universal-tv-remote-control-9202.html
</guid><description>
Universal TV Remote Control is an Android app that turns your smartphone or tablet into a remote control for your TV. Your Android device will become a TV remote control for Smart TV, Samsung, LG, Android TV, Roku, Fire TV, Sony, etc. You can control both Smart TV (using Wi-Fi) and Non-Smart TV (using IR Blaster).
Make your life a little easier by installing UniMote. Turn your smartphone into a remote control for your TV. User-friendly interface. It's basically the old remote control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.3.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:42:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicates Cleaner 4.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:42:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duplicates-cleaner-9126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duplicates-cleaner-9126.html
</guid><description>
Are you facing memory problems on your device? Is your device running out of memory? Do you want to increase the storage space on your device?, if "yes" then look no further and hit that "install" button.
Efficient Duplicate Cleaner: Find and clean up "Genuine" duplicate images, duplicate audio files, duplicate Videos and duplicate documents in the simplest way!, Our Duplicate Cleaner app uses advanced proprietary techniques to quickly identify and remove "Genuine Duplicates" from your...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAVx⁵ – CalDAV CardDAV WebDAV 4.5.3-gplay</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:41:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html
</guid><description>
DAVx is the only all-in-one app for everything CalDAV, CardDAV and WebDAV! This is a full-featured synchronization solution for your contacts (CardDAV), calendar (CalDAV), and tasks (based on VTODO). The app is easy to install and integrates seamlessly with your favorite calendar/contacts apps (including default apps). It can also be used separately if you have CalDAV, CardDAV or just Tasks. DAVx can also be used to access your remote WebDAV files.
Features of DAVx for Android
	Sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.80</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:40:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download QRbot: QR &amp;amp; barcode reader 3.2.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:36:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qrbot-qr-barcode-reader-8737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qrbot-qr-barcode-reader-8737.html
</guid><description>
Scan all types of QR codes and barcodes with QRBot's QR code reader. Quickly access your scanning-related functions: For example, add contact data to your address book or connect to a WiFi hotspot with just one click. Easily share arbitrary data such as website links by displaying them on your screen as QR codes and scanning them with another device.
Supported QR codes 
	Website links (URLs)
	Contact data (Mecard, Vcard, VCF)
	Calendar events
	WiFi hotspot access...
</description></item></channel></rss>