<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:38:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:38:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.6 Build 92479</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:29:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Music Studio 12.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:29:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Music Studio is software to work with audio files. Includes the process of taking the disc recording CD, DVD and Blu-ray discs module to organize music collections, editing audio files, recording module and the tool to restore audio files broken.
Ashampoo Music Studio
Functions of Ashampoo Music Studio
	Edit audio files quickly
	Cut perfect slices including direct recording
	Convert to any format and listen anywhere
	The most convenient tool to extract CD
	Create a list from...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Aquarium Screensaver 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-aquarium-screensaver-14538.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-aquarium-screensaver-14538.html
</guid><description>
AI Aquarium Screensaver is a realistic 3D screen saver that transforms your idle screen into a vibrant underwater world. Powered by AI-controlled fish behavior, it delivers smooth, natural motion and non-repetitive scenes – making it the ideal relaxing screen saver for Windows desktops, offices, and large screens.
With a wide selection of beautifully designed aquarium wallpapers, including rock arches, rainforests, coral reefs, Dutch-style aquariums, cartoon worlds, and electronic...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:28:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Privacy Inspector 3.00.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:28:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html
</guid><description>
Windows keeps extensive records of what you do and when you do it on your PC (offline and online). So what is logged and more importantly, what can you do about it? Ashampoo Privacy Inspector lifts the veil of secrecy and shows you exactly what activities are logged along with the ability to erase your data and regain your privacy.
Features of Ashampoo Privacy Inspector
	See used objects neatly organized
	Delete confidential usage data securely
	Analysis of browsing behavior for all...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:27:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.1.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:27:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:26:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PreviSat 7.2.1.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:26:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-previsat-3144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-previsat-3144.html
</guid><description>
PreviSat is software satellite tracking with the aim of helping you to monitor and observe the position of artificial satellites in real-time. This tool can make predictions about the passes of the satellites and Iridium flares. There are also a number of parameters integrated help you collect important information about the location of satellites in the different frames, the elements of appraisal (elements of Keplerian orbits), TLE (element two lines) is set to calculate the location of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.1.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:25:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Clear 26.1.10738</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:24:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html
</guid><description>
AVG Clear is free program help completely erase everything from installing AVG current your including the registry entries, file, settings, files, users, etc. AVG Clear is provided by AVG and is the last measure to use if you encounter a problem when deleting AVG current whether it is error repair, reinstall, or delete altogether.
Please note that all user settings AVG will be removed after the uninstall process is complete. The items should be deleted to include content from Virus...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.1.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:24:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dragonrise Games YoloX 1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:23:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html
</guid><description>
Use YoloX to change your game crosshair.Including color inversion, sound sensor, motion sensor, heat safety and other features never seen before.Development your target with the next revolution in crosshair technology!
YoloX Features
	Effect: Invert colors and other effects.
	Animation: Separate animations for primary fire, secondary fire, and jump.
	Sound sensor: Animated response to game sounds. Now you can listen to your own music without missing any key sounds.
	Motion sensor:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moneyspire 2026 v26.0.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:22:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html
</guid><description>
Moneyspire is a personal and small business finance management program that lets you track your basic accounts, budgets, bills, loans, and investments. Categorize your spending and income into customizable categories. Track bills so you never forget to pay and avoid late fees. Set budgets to track spending and avoid overspending in specific categories like eating out. Forecast account balances to avoid overdrafts and cash shortages. Balance your checkbook and compare it to your bank...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.1.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:22:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download RepairKit 1.3.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html
</guid><description>
RepairKit is an all-in-one Java-based Windows repair and maintenance toolkit. RepairKit aims to provide a package that provides users with a dedicated system repair tool as well as quick access to some operating system features and some other PC maintenance software that comes with it. it.
If you want to keep your PC running smoothly and want to do it conveniently, RepairKit offers a simple and effective solution for that, with an automatic repair/cleanup module , as well as access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Video Editor 19.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:38:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giliSoft-video-editor-37.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giliSoft-video-editor-37.html
</guid><description>
Software GiliSoft Video Editor supports editing video files in many formats such as AVI, MPEG, H. 264, SWF, MOV, WMV,... to run on popular devices like iPod, iPhone, PSP, PS3,....
Besides it also provides for users a lot of effects to help you edit brightness, contrast as well as saturation for his videos. Lots of different filters to help you get the perfect video the most. In particular, GiliSoft Video Editor also feature support insert watermark for your video. With this feature you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3069</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blank And Secure 8.31</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html
</guid><description>
Blank And Secure is a application lightweight and portable allows you to completely erase your sensitive data without possibility to restore. This add-on accomplish this by overwriting your files with zeros (0) before you delete them. This method is also called "zeroing data / drives". You should know that once completed, the complete data can't be recovered, so you should only use this tool if you want to permanently delete your files.
Blank And Secure - Delete data permanently
Blank...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster JPG to PDF Converter 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:36:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-jpg-to-pdf-converter-9640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-jpg-to-pdf-converter-9640.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster JPG to PDF Converter is a software application developed by Coolmuster Studio. As the name suggests, it is designed to convert JPG (JPEG) image files into PDF files. The software provides a simple and convenient way to convert individual or multiple JPG files into a single PDF document.
Whether you have JPEG, PNG, TIFF or BMP files, the software's advanced algorithms maintain image quality, color accuracy, and resolution when converting them to PDF. Users can rely on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaInfo 26.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:36:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html
</guid><description>
MediaInfo is a software that provides access to view the information of media files, such as technical information and tags of the video file and bad sound. Software displays detailed information including: format, profile, commercial name of the format, duration, bit rate overall, writing application and library, title, author, director, album, track number, updates.
MediaInfo - View file info media
The features and functions of MediaInfo
	Container: format, profile, commercial name...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Downloader 4.0.0.79</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:35:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Downloader is a support program download quick video of genuine FastPcTools. ast Video Downloader is an easy to use program that allows you to download desired videos from a number of sites online storage. I think that I will not reveal secret if they write that most of the sites have video archives do not contain the ability to download videos and sometimes that's very necessary. This is when the same program is rescue, this allows you to save videos from the archive page as...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition 19.23.0 Build 202601261108</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:35:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition is a version plugins help you to create a disk partition on WinPE for you to easily recover hard drive partition computer if not may broken or error. Boot disk EasUS Partition Master WinPE, format software mobile, you can:
	Works well in Windows, such as extend system partition or settling low disk space and managing disk space, recovery partition deleted , rebuild MBR, restore partition GPT, etc.
	You are allowed to resize the primary drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF to JPG Converter 2.5.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:34:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-jpg-converter-9593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-jpg-converter-9593.html
</guid><description>
Convert PDF to high quality JPG, PNG, TIF, BMP and GIF images easily with Coolmuster PDF to JPG Converter. Coolmuster PDF to JPG Converter easily converts your PDF files into stunning images with just a few clicks, making it easy to work with your PDF content in a visually appealing way. It allows you to convert from PDF to JPG/JPEG, PDF to PNG, PDF to TIF, PDF to GIF, PDF to BMP.
You can select specific pages or range of pages without limitation and convert multiple PDF files to image...
</description></item></channel></rss>