<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:46:42 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:46:42 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ADV Screen Recorder 4.20.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:46:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adv-screen-recorder-10150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adv-screen-recorder-10150.html
</guid><description>
Need to record your screen easily and without a menu covering the entire screen? ADV Screen Recorder is designed to be fully featured, without any limitations, and without root required.
ADV screen recorder allows you
	Record with 2 tools (Default and Advanced)
	Pause recording (Requires advanced tools)
	Draw quickly with your favorite colors
	Use Camera before or after recording
	Place your text with full customization
	Place your Banner with full customization
	Cut video.
</description></item><item><title>Download UnWX (Severe Weather Alerts) 5.3.1 Build 276</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:46:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unwx-severe-weather-alerts-14064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unwx-severe-weather-alerts-14064.html
</guid><description>
This app will alert you when severe weather is likely. Alerts are issued from official sources when weather conditions are likely to pose a danger to life and property. In addition, the application also integrates a probability indicator (if available).
Depending on the country, the application will warn of weather hazards such as tornadoes, cyclones, thunderstorms, hail, heavy rain, snow, ice, slippery, heat, strong winds, fog, floods or sea warnings.
Features:
	Warnings for all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cast to TV, Chromcast &amp;amp;amp; Roku 2.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:45:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cast-to-tv-chromcast-roku-11459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cast-to-tv-chromcast-roku-11459.html
</guid><description>
Cast to TV, Chromcast &amp;amp; Roku lets you cast online videos and all your local videos, music and pictures to your TV, Chromecast, Roku, Amazon Fire Stick or Fire TV, Xbox, Apple TV or other Devices Other DLNA. Cast to TV and stream videos and movies on TV now!
Easy to connect and stream to Roku. You can stream videos and music to Roku without limitations. Fast forwarding and rewinding can bring you a wonderful experience when watching movies. Cast local videos, photo slideshows, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sleep Cycle: Sleep Tracker 4.25.41-production</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:45:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-cycle-sleep-tracker-8151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-cycle-sleep-tracker-8151.html
</guid><description>
Sleep cycle: A sleep tracker is a mobile app that uses sensors on your phone to track your sleep patterns and wake you at the optimal time in your sleep cycle. The app analyzes your sleep patterns and wakes you up in 30-minute intervals when you are in light sleep, which is the natural waking phase of your sleep cycle. This helps you feel more rested and refreshed when you wake up. Sleep cycle: Sleep tracker also includes features like a sleep diary, snore tracker, and sleep notes,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bundled Notes - List, Organize 4.0.1-001</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:45:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bundled-notes-list-organize-13704.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bundled-notes-list-organize-13704.html
</guid><description>
Organize everything - from personal notes, lists, and projects to movie watchlists, recipes, bookmarks, and more Whether you keep your notes and lists simple or like to customize them to meet all your organizational needs, Bundled Notes is the app for you.
Key Features:
	Beautiful Material Design You Design With Dynamic Themes
	Ad-Free Experience
	Seamless Syncing Across Devices equipped
	Markdown support with visual formatting
	Powerful organization with “bundles”
	Kanban board...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balance: Meditation &amp;amp; Sleep 1.189.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html
</guid><description>
Improve stress, sleep and more with the world's first personalized meditation program. Balance is your personal meditation coach. Each day, you will answer questions about your meditation experience, goals, and interests. Using an audio library of thousands of files, Balance puts together the perfect daily meditation for you. The more you share over time, the more personalized and effective your meditation becomes.
Balance's daily meditation sessions are organized according to a 10-Day...
</description></item><item><title>Download Peak – Brain Games &amp;amp; Training 4.29.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:44:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html
</guid><description>
Peak is a brain training application aimed at improving cognitive abilities and brain activity. It has many games and exercises designed to target different areas of the brain such as memory, attention, problem solving and more. It only takes 10 minutes a day to complete a brain training exercise. And, with 45 brain games for adults and new brain training exercises every day, there's always a fun challenge waiting for you.
Some features of the application include:
	Daily brain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.1.3 beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:43:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 217.14873.20251022.rc</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:43:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download IMDb: Movies &amp;amp; TV Shows 9.2.2.109220800</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:43:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html
</guid><description>
IMDb (Internet Movie Database) is a popular application that provides information about movies, TV shows, and other video content. This app allows users to search and browse information about a variety of movies and TV shows, including cast and crew information, user ratings and reviews, trailers, and more. Users can also create watchlists and rate the movies and shows they've watched.
Some key features of the IMDb application include:
	Browse movies and TV shows by popularity,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flashlight Plus: Bright Light 2.8.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:42:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html
</guid><description>
Turn your mobile phone into a flashlight and a magnifying glass! This is a new flashlight app. This smart two-in-one app has both a flashlight and a magnifying glass. OpticView™ lets you see what you're lighting on the screen, turning your phone into one of the most compact and powerful gadgets you've ever owned!
Features
	A simple and free flashlight app, great for emergencies
	Use your device's LED as a torch and bring the brightest flashlight on your phone!
	Turn on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photographer's companion Pro 2.0.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:42:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photographers-companion-pro-8352.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photographers-companion-pro-8352.html
</guid><description>
This app will help you give up the auto mode that doesn't do everything and control the camera's everything. For more experienced photographers, it can simplify settings by doing the calculations for you. In any case, it's not a magic app for creating great photos every time, but it will let you find a basic setting to tweak to get the best photo you think.
Features of Photographer's companion Pro
	Calculating alternative/equivalent exposures (managing ND filters and long...
</description></item><item><title>Download PlayerPro Music Player 5.39 build 245</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:42:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-playerpro-music-player-9862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-playerpro-music-player-9862.html
</guid><description>
PlayerPro Music Player is a feature-rich music player application available for Android devices. It is developed by BlastOn SA and offers a comprehensive set of features designed to enhance the music listening experience. PlayerPro features a beautiful, fast and intuitive interface, alongside powerful audio configuration options. In addition, there is a choice of several free plugins to complement it: Skins, DSP Pack...
Features of PlayerPro Music Player
	Browse and play your music in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Powerful RAM Monitor Pro 11.10.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:41:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerful-cleaner-pro-9435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerful-cleaner-pro-9435.html
</guid><description>
Powerful Cleaner Pro is a mobile app designed to optimize and improve the performance of Android devices. This app helps users clean up junk files, remove unused apps, and manage their device's storage space, resulting in faster and smoother performance.
With the powerful Cleaner Pro, users can easily scan their devices for junk files, temporary files, and cache files and delete them with a single tap. The app also allows users to uninstall apps that they no longer need and to clear the...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Monitor Cpu Ram Battery 11.10.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:41:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-system-monitor-cpu-ram-booster-8783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-system-monitor-cpu-ram-booster-8783.html
</guid><description>
System Monitor CPU RAM Booster is the most powerful System Monitor for Android, Including: CPU Monitor, Storage Cleaner, Memory Booster, Battery Doctor, Battery Saver. Developed by Andro IX, The App Provides Detailed Information About The Device's CPU, RAM, Storage, Battery, and Network Usage, Allowing Users To Identify and Troubleshoot Performance Issues.
System Monitor Proved many Kinds of Powerful Tools, Including: RAM Booster and Cleaner, Overheating Alarm, Overheating Protection,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery manager and monitor 11.10.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:41:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-manager-and-monitor-10216.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-manager-and-monitor-10216.html
</guid><description>
The most beautiful and powerful battery manager for Android! Include Battery Monitor and Battery saver. Battery Manager Provides many Kinds of Tools. Including: One Tap Boost, RAM Widget, CPU Widget, Battery Widget, Desktop Floating Window, Status Bar Floating Window, Over Heat Alarm. You can monitor the ram, CPU and Battery Information Very Convenient. The detail features including
Features of Battery Manager and Monitor
	Battery Monitor: Show The Curve of Battery Usage and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Graphing Calculator - Algeo 2.46</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:40:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-graphing-calculator-algeo-8784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-graphing-calculator-algeo-8784.html
</guid><description>
Algeo is the most beautiful scientific graphing calculator available on the Play Store. It's fast and powerful and you'll never have to carry a large physical TI calculator again. The intuitive interface displays your drawn functions as if you wrote them on paper instead of putting everything on one line. And you don't need an internet connection unlike other graphing calculators, it works offline too! Useful for calculus, physics or solving those x+y equations.
This free app has more...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.19</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:40:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyRadar Weather Radar Premium 8.66.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myradar-weather-radar-8127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myradar-weather-radar-8127.html
</guid><description>
MyRadar is a weather monitoring and forecasting application for Android devices. It provides users with real-time weather information, including radar maps, current conditions, and forecasts for locations around the world. To use MyRadar, users must download the app from the Google Play Store or other Android app store or taiwebs.com.
Features of MyRadar Weather Radar Pro APK
	Animated radar map shows the movement of precipitation over time
	Current temperature, humidity, and wind...
</description></item><item><title>Download Download video no watermark 1.47.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:39:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-download-video-no-watermark-13999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-download-video-no-watermark-13999.html
</guid><description>
Want to download videos without watermark? Try Video Downloader for TT No Watermark (Pinterest Video Downloader)! You can freely set live wallpaper and ringtone by downloading your favorite music or videos! Download any videos and music you like on TT and watch them offline. Fast and Easy!
Highlight Features
	Video Downloader for TT (Pinterest Video Downloader): No need to log in.
	Set live wallpaper and ringtone is simple and free.
	Download Pinterest mp4 videos, Download CapCut...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker 16.15.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:39:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html
</guid><description>
Join a community that helps people escape difficulties and stick with running forever! Track your workouts, set goals, sweat, and see your progress. Whether you're trying to track a 5K goal or train for a marathon, use the GPS app trusted by 50 million users and counting.
ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker is a mobile application that allows users to track running and fitness activities on their Android devices. The app uses GPS to track the user's distance, pace, and running time as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transparent clock weather Pro 8.99.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:38:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html
</guid><description>
Transparent Clock Weather Pro: Get Accurate Local or Worldwide Weather Forecasts Easily with Live Weather Updates, Hourly and Daily Weather Forecasts and Timely Weather Alerts. Check The Weather for Today, Tomorrow or the weekend with our Easy to use app and widgets.
Features of Transparent Clock Weather Pro
	local Weather: Automatically keep track or your location as you move and get accurate real time weather reports and alerts
	Different Weather Preded for More Accurate Weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blender 4.5.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:16:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download FurMark 2.10.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:41:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html
</guid><description>
FurMark is free software to help check the operation of the computer graphics card at the same time can emulator the situation, unplanned incidents of the CPU, the video card to you have how to handle best. FurMark allows you to set resolutions that card check will pass directly, you can perform both in full-screen mode and window, there are many parameters smoothing, in general, have enough parameters, you just need to artfully place them and you can immediately proceed to check out. If...
</description></item><item><title>Download NVIDIA App 11.0.5.420</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:35:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html
</guid><description>
NVIDIA App is an indispensable companion for PC gamers and creators. Make sure your PC is always updated with the latest NVIDIA drivers and technology. Optimize your games and apps with the new unified GPU control center, capture your favorite moments with powerful recording tools through in-game overlays, and explore new tools and features. Latest NVIDIA software.
The program consists of two main parts
	Game Ready Drivers: GeForce Game Ready Drivers are fine-tuned in collaboration...
</description></item></channel></rss>