<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:31:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:31:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 10.27.24.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:48:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download OnlyOffice Desktop Editors 9.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:27:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html
</guid><description>
OnlyOffice is a free office suite that can open documents, presentations, and spreadsheets in different tabs of the same window, providing interoperability Compatible with the most popular file formats. With an attractive intuitive interface and intuitive controls, OnlyOffice allows users to open documents, spreadsheets and presentations, or create new ones from scratch. It comes with support for the most common file formats, even those native to Microsoft's office suite. Moreover, it can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.551</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:26:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro 25H2 v26200.6899 NoTPM Preactivated</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:21:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is officially leaked to a developer version. Previously, when Windows 10 was released, Microsoft once stated that Windows 10 would be the last version of Windows for users. Clearly, with the arrival of Windows 11, Microsoft needed a major reason to reverse its previous claims and still remove Windows 10 by introducing some new operating systems.
About the interface of Windows 11 is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 has stopped growing). The logo image of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2509 Build 19231.20194 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:20:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Video Converter 31.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:20:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Video Converter is a software to convert Video DVD to the Video format the other with fast speed. Convenient program to convert the popular video formats and movie DVD, download WonderFox DVD Video Converter below. You can create videos that will be optimized for viewing on mobile devices. There is a simple video editor, it will allow you to add effects, crop photos, and etc.
WonderFox DVD Video Converter
WonderFox DVD Video Converter support rip DVD and videos to various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2024 Professional Plus LTSC v2408 Build 17932.20574 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:19:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft has officially announced the final version of the Office 2024 release for Windows and Mac users. After releasing a preview version in the first half of this year, the product has been finalized and is now available to users. Office 2024 includes updated versions of apps from the Word 2024, Excel 2024, PowerPoint 2024, Outlook 2024, Access 2024, and Publisher 2024 suites.
Office 2024 includes virtually every change that has been added to the suite of programs in Office 365 over...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.9.25.11 x64 / 4.2.3.28 x86</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:18:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Ripper Pro 24.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:17:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-ripper-pro-2066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-ripper-pro-2066.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Ripper is a tool to extract DVD fast number 1 really, only takes about 20 minutes to extract DVD 150 minutes to MP4, AVI, MKV, MOV, WMV with 0-quality loss and takes less time to MPG (only 5 ~ 10 minutes). Moreover, it complements the presets are optimized for all mobile devices pop as DVD to iPhone 5S, iPad Air, iPad mini 3, DVD to Samsung Galaxy S5, Sony, Nokia, BlackBerry, HTC, Xbox, Android devices, etc. WonderFox DVD Ripper Pro provides the best solution to convert DVD...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:16:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.48 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:16:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office 2021 Professional Plus (64-bit) LTSC v2108 Build 14334.20344 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:15:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-2021-64-bit-7187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-2021-64-bit-7187.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft 365 is a subscription that comes with premium apps like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, OneNote, Outlook, Publisher, and Access (Publisher and Access are available on PC only). Applications can be installed on a variety of devices, including PCs, Macs, iPads, iPhones, tablets, and Android phones. Microsoft 365 also comes with services like 1 TB OneDrive storage, 60 Skype minutes per month, and Microsoft support by phone and chat. When you're on a subscription, you'll receive the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro 28.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:14:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro is a software powerful video conversion . This program can convert the video files the quality standard of the file SD card, the files HD as HD MP4, HD MKV, HD AVI, HD MTS, HD TRP. This can also in the opposite direction. This software includes more than 100 video formats, while maintaining quality output, faster than 50 times compared to some software. This software also supports VBR or VBR, using this option will keep the original quality of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.17 (1410)</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:13:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download imyPass Windows Password Reset 1.0.16 (Platinum / Ultimate)</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:12:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imypass-windows-password-reset-6726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imypass-windows-password-reset-6726.html
</guid><description>
imyPass Windows Password Reset is a world-class Windows password reset tool to reset the standard user account password and Windows Administrator on Windows 10/8.1/8/7/XP/Vista without losing data. Besides reordering the password, it is capable of creating new accounts through a CD/DVD or USB drive.
How imyPass Windows Password Reset Works:
Do not need any complex settings or help, imyPass Windows Password Reset provides you with 2 ways to reset your password on Windows via CD/DVD and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnkhTech WinPE Lite 2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:12:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-winpe-lite-14011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-winpe-lite-14011.html
</guid><description>
AnkhTech WinPE Lite is a compact, lightweight version of WinPE that supports almost any hardware and has a huge number of programs! It is used to maintain any type of personal computer or laptop, and as an IT technician, it makes your job a lot easier!
This environment allows booting from a USB flash drive or DVD, providing access to a mini Windows operating system based on Windows 10 or 11, similar to the full Microsoft Windows interface. It includes a large number of pre-installed and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.17 (1410)</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:11:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.228</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:11:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio 20.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:11:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html
</guid><description>
Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio is the world's most advanced compositing software for visual effects artists, broadcast and motion graphics designers, and 3D animators. For the past 30 years, Fusion has been used on thousands of Hollywood blockbuster films and television shows. Fusion features a powerful node-based interface that lets you quickly and easily create sophisticated effects by connecting different types of image processing tools together! You get a wide range of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.10.15</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:09:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional 2.000</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:08:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional is a user-friendly Windows software designed to quickly create stunning slideshow videos from your photos. Ideal for both beginners and professionals, the software offers an intuitive drag-and-drop interface for arranging images, setting display durations, and adding individual subtitles or captions for personalization.
Key features include:
	Over 200 built-in transition effects such as soft fades, dynamic zooms, and creative animations for changing...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderPen 3.0.3.8120</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:08:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html
</guid><description>
WonderPen is a writing app for both professional and amateur writers. WonderPen uses a tree directory to organize documents, supports unlimited levels, and can easily manage both short articles and long works. Documents can be exported to various formats such as images, PDF, Word, Epub and web pages. Multiple chapters can be exported as a book in batches.
WonderPen has a built-in full automatic backup function. By default, it will perform a full database backup every 15 minutes. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.2 Build 1237</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:07:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yellow Leads Extractor 9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:06:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html
</guid><description>
Yellow Leads Extractor is the software that allows users to make 100% custom search in the browser. When you have this program then you don't need to do more work to retrieve information from the yellow pages. You just need to enter the category and location. After entering the information when you will click on the option data get then all the information will be extracted.
Yellow Leads Extractor - custom Search on the browser
The features of the Yellow Leads Extractor
	You can save...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.145</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:05:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item></channel></rss>