<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:40:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:40:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.12</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:40:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.40.564</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:39:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.40.564</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools MultiDocs 25.10.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:30:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-1909.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-1909.html
</guid><description>
FX Draw Tools to provide an environment to draw high productivity is exclusively designed for math teachers. Quickly create editable, high quality diagrams for the quiz, test, worksheets, web pages, presentations and demonstrations. FX Sketch, free extension of FX Draw Tools, allows you to sketch diagrams math and to them automatically converted into the drawing of professional quality can be edited by the power of FX Draw. Efofex also provides for the registration FX Draw three bonus...
</description></item><item><title>Download MeinPlatz 8.51</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:29:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html
</guid><description>
MeinPlatz is a free software provides an easy and fast way to scan the hard disk to find the disk space lost. After the search is complete, results can be exported to XLS, HTM, CSV and TXT. MeinPlatz "My-Place" also has a print function with preview feature integrated print and frame rate change, and is also a magnifying glass the small screen.
MeinPlatz - Scan disk
The new features of MeinPlatz
	General optimization and general improvements as well as update the file language in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Music and Video Downloader 3.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:29:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html
</guid><description>
Free Music &amp;amp; Video Downloader (formerly the Free Music Downloader) allows you to download his favorite music at the form of MP3 files from many different online sources, including Last.FM, Grooveshark, Sogou, VKontakte, SoundCloud, and many other things.Just enter name of artist or song you are looking for and click the Search button to see a list of results and download the songs you want.You can customize the services that applications will use to search, put the download folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disney Mickey's Typing Adventure Gold 3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:28:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disney-mickeys-typing-adventure-gold-10569.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disney-mickeys-typing-adventure-gold-10569.html
</guid><description>
Disney Mickey's Typing Adventure Gold is the most advanced typing program available recommended for ages 5 to 8. It presents Disney's Typing Adventures in full-screen size and rich color with graphics Beautiful animations provide optimal typing experience for kids. No other Typing tutorial is more motivating in educating learners.
Features of Disney Mickey's Typing Adventure Gold
Full of motivation
	Kids are motivated to learn new keys, pass typing tests, and complete challenges to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.5.7.993</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:28:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download NETworkManager 2025.10.18.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:25:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-networkmanager-3328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-networkmanager-3328.html
</guid><description>
NETworkManager is an open-Source tool that allows you to manage the network and troubleshoot the network. NETworkManager focus a number of tools can support managing network connections. You are granted access to a large assortment of tools available from the main window of NETworkManuber to effective use. You can use this tool to view network interface along with many bit other essential information such as IP address, DNS server, etc.). The network Card is connected can be configured...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nutrient Document Searchability (Tagging) 1.4.2509.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nutrient-document-searchability-tagging-14242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nutrient-document-searchability-tagging-14242.html
</guid><description>
Nutrient Document Searchability Tagging is a tool that enhances document searchability and classification in SharePoint by automatically generating and tagging metadata based on the content of the document through rules, taxonomies, barcodes, PDF and XMP forms, and integration with NLP services.
Easier document searchability tagging in 3 steps
	Documents are downloaded from SharePoint to a temporary location defined in Tagging.
	Meta Data is extracted or generated from the document...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thea For Rhino 4.5.257.168 for Rhino 6-9</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:31:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thea-for-rhino-5202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thea-for-rhino-5202.html
</guid><description>
Thea For Rhino is a professional tool, providing advanced features such as the interactive materials based on real physics, layered material improvements, support light IES &amp;amp; HDRI, along with the flexible tools including GPU biased, unbiased and GPU, rendered in Rhino was really strong. Thea For Rhino can be used to the interactive side in the Rhino Viewports. Select the Viewport desired and only need to the tool Thea Render gives you a picture immediately on sight of you.
Thea For...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:34:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PMAS - PowerShell Multi Activation System 6.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:34:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html
</guid><description>
This advanced PowerShell script is a flexible and modular solution designed for licensing Windows and Office products. It runs a custom .NET library called LibTSforge.dll directly from memory to license Office. It can work in GUI mode or silent mode.
Features
	License management for both Windows and Office products
	Generate product keys with the help of LibTSforge.dll
	User-friendly graphical options with Out-GridView
	Compatible with KMS, MAK, RETAIL, OEM, AVMA license types
	In...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2531</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:27:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.113</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fotosizer Professional 3.20.0.590</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:26:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html
</guid><description>
Fotosizer is a photo editing tool / photo series. It lets you resize hundreds of photos in few minutes quickly and easily. Increasingly, sharing photos on the internet is becoming increasingly popular. Image, is represented as JPEG files from digital cameras, taken at high resolution too big to send over the Internet, with some photos ending at 5 mega bytes. Upload photos to a website share photos is good, but 10, 20, or even more, this can last forever, especially on a dial-up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:26:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download RustDesk 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:25:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html
</guid><description>
RustDesk is a full-featured open source remote alternative for self-hosting and security with minimal configuration. It allows users to access and control their computers remotely from anywhere in the world, providing a convenient solution for remote work, technical support, or accessing files and applications on the go. transfer.
RustDesk is continuously updated and improved, providing a reliable and effective remote desktop solution. Whether you work remotely, need remote technical...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plagius Professional 2.9.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:25:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html
</guid><description>
Plagius Professional is a tool capable of analyzing documents and notifying the user in case of plagiarism detection. The program automatically generates reports after checking documents or web pages and supports rendering reports into HTML files for later analysis. Plagius Professional supports several file formats, such as PDF, TXT, RTF, HTML, HTM, ODT, SXW, DOCX or DOC, but for the last two formats you need to have Microsoft Word installed on your PC (otherwise, they can't be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 51</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:24:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.229</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:24:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Core Temp 1.19.5.69</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:23:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-core-temp-2229.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-core-temp-2229.html
</guid><description>
Core Temp is a simple utility capable of displaying the temperature of your processor online after the start, when the load on it changes, the temperature also will change. You can see the temperature for each core processor, if you have core multi-core. Core Temp will work perfectly on every motherboard. This program is mobile.
Core Temp - Displays the temperature of CPU computer
This feature will help you take the measures timely processing when the temperature up too high,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RiDoc 5.0.14.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:21:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ridoc-3999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ridoc-3999.html
</guid><description>
RiDoc is a program to grab images from a scanner and reduce the size of the image file. This program reduces the file size of documents or electronic images without reducing image quality. With the help of the assembly function, the frame images in accordance with page format A4 size and an image file is reduced without reducing image quality. The convergence of documents into graphical format to help protect these documents from unauthorized copying. To increase the level of protective...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus Portable 25.3.3.0232</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-plus-portable-12527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-plus-portable-12527.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus Portable is a cross-platform application that allows you to save high-quality videos from YouTube and other websites in seconds. This app works faster than any free online video downloader — just one click and you can enjoy content anytime, anywhere.
Save private clips and playlists that you have access to. Download private videos not only from YouTube but also from Facebook, Vimeo, Bilibili and many other sites. Access and download login-protected media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item></channel></rss>