<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 19:54:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 19:54:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.21</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:59:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.5.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:59:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:58:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Watchdog Anti-Malware Premium / Business 4.3.450</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:58:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html
</guid><description>
Watchdog Anti-Malware is an anti-malware with many highly rated tools to help keep your computer safe. Watchdog Anti-Malware will help you with Advanced Malware Detection and Removal, Browser Hijacker Removal, Effective Rootkit and Bootkit Detection and Removal, Real-Time Protection, Anti-ransomware Protection Module.
Watchdog Anti-Malware is extremely optimized and lightweight. Software engineers designed it to work efficiently without having to tweak confusing settings. Just start...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.256.8191</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:57:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Dimension 4.1.6.4632 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:56:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Dimension CC 2019 is software for designing 2D and 3D to easily create 3D images are of high quality, made to combine the resources intuitive 2D and 3D in one product the actual environment. Purpose introduction of Adobe Dimension is to provide to developers the tools necessary to integrate assets in 2D and 3D without having to study the application complex and specialized. In other words, the program allows you to quickly and simple and creative image other combined 2D and 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.174 Final</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:56:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0600 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:55:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCatalog 2024.15.0.1115</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:54:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html
</guid><description>
WinCatalog 2018 is a software cataloguer multi-function for the disk, file, folder, and any objects not files. Not always easy to track the location of a number of files in your computer, especially if you have a huge collection of CD and DVD. If you are one of those users, then surely there will be appropriate tools to work with such a task. WinCatalog is a software utility designed to help you find documents and data from your computer by building an index that allows you immediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.64.224</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.64.224</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.9.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reuschtools CopyWin 4.73</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html
</guid><description>
Reuschtools CopyWin is a versatile program designed to copy the contents of your Windows drive, including all files and programs, to another drive, USB or MicroSD card. This is especially useful for upgrading or replacing storage hardware, as it simplifies the migration process. The tool does not require installation; it can be used by running the executable file, but requires administrative rights to operate. CopyWin also offers features like incremental backups after the initial backup,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opal 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opal-6966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opal-6966.html
</guid><description>
Opal is a free app to listen to relaxing music or combine multiple sounds with different volumes to create your own sound tracks. With Opal, you can choose the sounds (17 relaxing music tracks available) that you want to listen to, turn them on and you can listen and enjoy the music for as long as you want without interruption.
Alternatively, You can turn on a timer to turn off all music after a certain amount of time. An extremely useful feature when you are about to go to sleep. Opal...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinWay Resume Deluxe 14.00.022</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:52:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winway-resume-deluxe-7274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winway-resume-deluxe-7274.html
</guid><description>
WinWay Resume Deluxe is the right tool for the job, it helps you write, format and check your resume for you. With WinWay Resume Deluxe, you will easily find a job, prepare your resume, excel in an interview, and maximize your salary. Perfect for any career situation: career advancement, career change, return to the job market, working from home.
WinWay Resume Deluxe includes over 14,000 resume examples and 116,000+ job-specific phrases. Also create persuasive cover letters, promotional...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:51:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.6.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:51:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Converter 3.4.82.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:43:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-converter-9471.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-converter-9471.html
</guid><description>
Helium Converter is a free, fully functional helper application that allows you to convert your audio files to a variety of formats. It provides comprehensive support for converting from and to a variety of lossless and lossy music file formats. Most output formats also support volume normalization (non-destructive) which can be configured per encoder.
In addition, the music file tag content (meta data) is also converted and saved to the destination file. Conversion of DRM (copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced PortChecker 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:43:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-portchecker-11321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-portchecker-11321.html
</guid><description>
Advanced PortChecker is an application that you can use to scan IP addresses for open ports. You can scan both TCP and UDP ports (at the same time) to check whether they allow connections or not. Scan information is displayed in real time, meaning you can use it as soon as it's available!
Main features:
	Scan TCP ports
	Scan UDP ports
	Real-time scanning information
	Export as HTML
	Export as CSV
	Export as plain text
	Automatic updates
	Change GUI theme
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickTextPaste 9.33</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:42:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html
</guid><description>
QuickTextPaste is a mobile application that allows you to add (paste) the text to be predetermined quickly in any Microsoft Windows program through keyboard shortcuts. You can copy the software on any USB flash drive or other portable device and carry it with you whenever you have to automate the task, paste text messages quickly and easily without having to redo the installation steps.
QuickTextPaste - Create shortcut paste text
Although this app seems geared to users who have more...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.22.1987</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:42:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Professional 2025.2.109</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:41:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Enterprise is a GUI client and popular tool for managing and developing PostgreSQL databases. This PostgreSQL IDE allows users to create, develop and execute queries, edit and adapt code according to their requirements in a convenient and user-friendly interface.
Main features:
SQL Development
	Save your time and improve code quality when creating and editing queries with the following features
	PostgreSQL code completion
	Code format
	SQL Check SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download RoboTask 10.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:40:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html
</guid><description>
RoboTask is software that allows you to automate any task combination on your computer, from just launching applications, checking your email, moving or backup files to upload or download, email and more. The program allows easy task to create simple tasks, as well as highly complex automation, involving the IF/ELSE statements that have conditions, loops, customization variables, and other advanced options.
Just a few minutes with RoboTask will give you a lot of ideas about how you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.31.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:40:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccdbMerge 1.36.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:40:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html
</guid><description>
AccdbMerge is a reliable program that allows you to quickly combine information and structure from multiple Microsoft Access database files, in two projects. The application can perform advanced data segregation, to avoid duplicate entries. Furthermore, the program provides support for differential comparison of batch data.
AccdbMerge Features
	The software can open password-protected files and compare them in two parallel projects. You can save settings, in case you often work with...
</description></item></channel></rss>