<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:50:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:50:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:42:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026.2 v20.2.1.17865</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026.2 v20.2.1.17865</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:39:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026.2 v20.2.1.17865</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:39:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Image Resizer 7.5.0.142</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:38:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html
</guid><description>
Light Image Resizer or also known as VSO Image Resizer. This is a software support thumbnail resolution images or move images in your hard drive. Light Image Resizer helps people store photos and digital images on their PC and who want to resize, compress, convert, create copies, import or organize photos. Light Image Resizer is integrated into Windows Explorer, right-click on your pictures and start working on your photos.
Light Image Resizer - miniature high-resolution photos and sort...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:32:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.45.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.541</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 4.2.0 Build 20251219</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:30:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption 12.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:25:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-stick-encryption-886.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-stick-encryption-886.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption is software designed specifically to create a USB memory stick be protected by a password. GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption will create the protected area on the disk need to enter password to see contents. Data on the protected areas are encrypted by 256 bit AES on the move. Protected USB stick is fully autonomous and does not require any special software be installed on the computer.
GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption - encryption, protect USB card
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro 20.1.578</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:25:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro is software that helps you to delete sensitive data securely with safeguards against misuse of data. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro you can be sure that no data is put into the wrong hands. O&amp;amp;O SafeErase provides reliable solution to securely delete files sensitive security and provide you with data protection optimization. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase even hackers and spyware data can't restore the deleted files of your safety.
&amp;nbsp;O&amp;amp;O SafeErase is the solution...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21805</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:18:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download KLS Backup Professional 2025 v14.0.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:10:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html
</guid><description>
KLS Backup Professional is a tool to backup and synchronize powerful allows you to backup or synchronize your information with the local drive and network, cloud storage, media, CD and DVD, WebDAV and FTP server. The backup documents can be stored uncompressed or compressed in Zip format or 7z basic. Backup KLS can backup: files or folders from the local disk, database, network locations or cloud storage, the mailbox data and other specific program (profile). Management in turn can...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools MBOX Converter 8.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:09:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-mbox-converter-7688.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-mbox-converter-7688.html
</guid><description>
SysTools MBOX Converter is the ultimate solution for exporting Mozilla Thunderbird MBOX files in a variety of file formats. Its latest version is designed with many new features that provide users to unpack MBOX attachments and transfer their mailbox data in top shape.
Features of SysTools MBOX Converter
	Allow batch conversion of multiple MBOX files
	Ability to perform conversion of MBX/MBS files as well
	Multiple Export Formats: Outlook PST, MSG, EML, PDF, NSF, HTML
	Allow to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.582</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:04:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark SystemInfo 5.89.1404</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:04:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark SystemInfo is a small program created to conduct diagnostic analysis complete all kinds of processes, as well as equipment used on a personal computer of you. According to the author, you can use this tool as a component reference in the application be supported, it will determine the version of your operating system and other information about the hardware.
Note that Windows XP, 3DMark06, and PCMark05 are no longer be Futuremark support. Function SystemInfo on Windows XP is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.54</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:58:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download XToolBox 5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:57:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtoolbox-8700.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtoolbox-8700.html
</guid><description>
XToolBox is an open source tool that includes more than 50 applications to optimize and tweak Windows 10/11. If you're looking for an all-in-one utility to help streamline debugging and tweaking your machine with the added ability to download official and modified versions of Windows, this little app will suit you.
XToolBox will give you a centralized place to manage your system, like ADWCleaner, Malwarebytes, CleanMGR+, Defraggler, and others. The goal is to make it as simple as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download VX Search Ultimate 17.6.18 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:47:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vx-search-ultimate-enterprise-1476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vx-search-ultimate-enterprise-1476.html
</guid><description>
VX Search Ultimate is an automated file search solution, based on a rule that allows a person to search for file types, categories, file names, sizes, locations, extensions, formal expressions, text patterns and binary, create, modify, and date access, the EXIF card, etc. Users are offered the ability to classify and filter results, copy, move or delete files, save reports and export results to SQL databases.
VX Search allows a person to perform file search operations, review the search...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft KJ/DJ File Manager 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:47:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html
</guid><description>
KJ File Manager is a program that will allow you to easily manage the audio and video files in karaoke format, you can now record MP3 tags ID and edit metadata information, done all in batch mode.
Easily manage files karaoke, video and audio of you and fixes title easily with batch editing powerful. Support the format name standard most popular. Automatic fix for underscores and capitalization, swap title and artist, shift, split, and replace field data on multiple files at once,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverHub 1.5.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:41:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverhub-6486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverhub-6486.html
</guid><description>
DriverHub  is a tool that helps provide the user an efficient way to keep the drivers in the computer up to date. The driver storage facility in the cloud keeps updating the latest drivers and ensures that you always get the most relevant and latest.
DriverHub quickly scans your pc for any outdated drivers, then finds and displays the latest available drivers to install. It's important to make sure you have all the latest drivers installed, etc. on your device to keep it working...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.64.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:41:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:40:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item><item><title>Download LANDR Mastering Plugin Pro 1.1.35</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:40:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-landr-mastering-plugin-pro-13887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-landr-mastering-plugin-pro-13887.html
</guid><description>
LANDR Mastering Plugin Pro is an AI-powered professional mastering plugin designed to deliver fast, high-quality, customizable mastering directly in your Digital Audio Workstation (DAW). It integrates LANDR's decades of expertise in AI mastering technology, allowing users to create polished, release-ready masters while maintaining full control over the sound in real-time.
Key Features:
	AI-powered Mastering: Analyzes your tracks and creates three separate professional masters tailored...
</description></item></channel></rss>