<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 15:36:37 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 15:36:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.30</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:21:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:20:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Toon Boom Harmony Premium 25.0.1 Build 24106</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:20:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toon-boom-harmony-premium-2861.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toon-boom-harmony-premium-2861.html
</guid><description>
Toon Boom Harmony Premium is software recognized and used by animation studio leading the world in the last 25 years, the Harmony playground with the animation software produced by take 2D animations and the ability to produce full for students, collaborators, artists and professional illustrators alike.
Access the complete toolkit for animated frame by frame traditional. Toon Boom Harmony Premium is integrated to the 3D model animate and the individual parts of them live in Harmony...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.16.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:19:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.10.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:18:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.83.108</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:18:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xmanager Power Suite 8.0.0016</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:18:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html
</guid><description>
Xmanager Power Suite is the network connection complete. The products include: Xmanager (server, PC X high performance); Xshell (SSH client, strong); Xftp (client-SFTP / FTP); Xlpd (a print management tools work). Xmanager Power Suite is a solution all-in-one includes Xmanager, Xshell, Xftp and Xlpd in a single set. Xmanager run the app window X and Xshell manage servers Unix / Linux remotely with a terminal safety. Xftp transfers files between systems securely, and Xlpd runs in locally...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for SQL Server Enterprise 2025.2.37</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:17:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server is the program that will help the developer SQL management database, change database version control in the source control system downloads, speed up routine tasks, as well as perform the change database complicated.
A handy tool to analyze the status of the index SQL and troubleshoot issues with fragmentation index. dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server allows you to quickly collect statistical data fragmentation index and the current database needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v242</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:16:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyBurn Pro 6.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:16:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-pro-8828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-pro-8828.html
</guid><description>
AnyBurn Pro is disc burning software that allows users to create, burn and copy a variety of discs, including CDs, DVDs and Blu-ray discs. It also provides additional features such as creating, converting and mounting disk images. Exclusive features of AnyBurn Pro version:
	Convert Audio File Format
	Install Windows onto a USB drive
Features of AnyBurn Pro
	Burn Disc: AnyBurn Pro allows users to burn a variety of discs, including data, audio and video CDs, DVDs and Blu-ray discs....
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Toolkit 1.23.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:15:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Toolkit is software that provides the ability to automatically block HTTP and HTTPS traffic from most client applications, including web browsers such as Chrome and Firefox, most CLI tools and auxiliary languages such as Node.js, Python, Ruby etc. You can browse through traffic by marking the content type, status, and source or search by URL, status, and title to find important notifications.
You can check the URL, status, title, and content of each request or feedback, along with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Patch My PC 5.3.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:14:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html
</guid><description>
Patch My PC is a comprehensive application and reliable will provide the simple solution for managing patch party Tuesday. The category Enterprise SCUP will provide an incentive simple and unique about the updates and the application updates of the Tuesday easy and updated. The update application can be easily installed on your computer in a few minutes, through the function software updates are integrated into The configuration manager center system MS. No additional agent or server...
</description></item><item><title>Download save2pc Ultimate 5.7.5.1649</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:12:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-save2pc-ultimate-555.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-save2pc-ultimate-555.html
</guid><description>
save2pc Ultimate is software support download online videos from Youtube and over 30 other sharing website on your computer to view offline or share with others. Today, the emergence of numerous video sharing sites online, especially Youtube, watching videos online is very simple. But for some reason that you want to download them to your personal computer, then save2pc Ultimate will help you perform that job quickly, the most simple.
Save2pc Ultimate gives users the ability to download...
</description></item><item><title>Download KLS Backup Professional 2025 v14.0.2.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:12:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html
</guid><description>
KLS Backup Professional is a tool to backup and synchronize powerful allows you to backup or synchronize your information with the local drive and network, cloud storage, media, CD and DVD, WebDAV and FTP server. The backup documents can be stored uncompressed or compressed in Zip format or 7z basic. Backup KLS can backup: files or folders from the local disk, database, network locations or cloud storage, the mailbox data and other specific program (profile). Management in turn can...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.10.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:11:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package 6.1.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:11:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html
</guid><description>
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package is the package includes programs to work with video, audio, graphics, documents, and system cleaning. You can install as a complete package, or separate. Which program are presented: AVS Video Editor, AVS Video Converter, AVS Video ReMaker, AVS Media Player, AVS Audio Editor, AVS Audio Converter, AVS Disc Converter, AVS Image Converter, AVS Document Converter, AVS Registry Cleaner.
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package - Full set of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Prime 6.7.0.30</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:10:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softros LAN Messenger 12.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:09:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softros-lan-messenger-5063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softros-lan-messenger-5063.html
</guid><description>
Softros LAN Messenger is a messaging application LAN easy to use for internal communication, safe and effective. It does not require the server to run and very easy to install. Softros LAN Messenger comes with a variety of handy features such as messaging, PC-PC, chat room, LAN, group messaging promoting to quickly notify the individual or group is selected on an event and file transfer drag and drop to exchange files and folders between staff members.
The features of Softros LAN...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCode 2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:09:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccode-12736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccode-12736.html
</guid><description>
CCode is a free source code editor based on Scintilla, a code editor developed by Yubsoft. CCode is written in C++ with about 24000 lines of code, no MFC, no WTL, no QT, just pure Win32 and C++, to keep the software small and fast.
Features
	Built-in file explorer
	Fully featured tab-based code editor
	Code snippets
	Symbol list
	Automatic code indentation
	Code hints
	Favorite files and folders
	Runs on 32-bit and 64-bit versions of Windows from Windows XP to Windows 11
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:08:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.9.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:07:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezAccounting 3.15.15</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html
</guid><description>
ezAccounting is accounting software designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. ezAccounting is the solution internal accounting suitable for small businesses need to record and report on cash flow in and out including sales, incomes and expenses and purchases. It also supports payroll processing and print tax forms.
The features of ezAccounting
	Company accounts unlimited
	Custom format form
	Custom format Czech
	Support multiple tax code
	Support multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Homedale 2.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:06:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html
</guid><description>
Homedale is a screen wireless network simple allows you to view the status and signal strength of nearby access points. In addition to displaying technical information like infrastructure, channels and bitrate are supported, the program also includes a chart signals allows you to monitor signal strength of multiple access points in real time.
Because this is a mobile program, it is important to mention that it does not leave any traces in the Windows Registry. You can copy it on any USB...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyBurn 6.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:06:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-1165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-1165.html
</guid><description>
AnyBurn is software to burn CD, DVD and Blu-ray helps you easily create disk images and software synthesis of multimedia or USB drive can boot. As far as installation, you can make the tool verify written data, eject the disc after recording, as well as finalize the disc (an option required by media player). The application supports many image files, such as ISO, DAA, BIN, MDF, MDS, NRG, CDI, IMG, UIF and WIM.
AnyBurn - Create disc DVD, Blu-ray
In addition, you can create audio CD from...
</description></item><item><title>Download KiCad 9.0.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:06:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html
</guid><description>
KiCad is a unique software product that allows you to open, create and develop electronic circuits for subsequent visualization of printed circuit board designs in interactive views . It allows you to develop complex circuit diagrams using an electronic components database and test signal integrity. It includes free applications, facilities, templates, and open libraries.
Using KiCad, users will be able to create truly professional printed circuit board layouts, beautifully designed...
</description></item></channel></rss>