<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:48:26 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:48:26 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.103.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:10:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:09:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.19.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU-Z 2.68</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-1144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-1144.html
</guid><description>
GPU-Z is a compact utility, simple help display parameters GPU and video Card the computer. GPU-Z to display information adapter details, Bios version, memory details, overclock, default clock, 3D clock, and much more. Besides, the program also includes check download GPU to verify configuration lane PCI-Express, as well as monitoring sensors in real time.
GPU-Z - information Display, GPU and display Card
Features of GPU-Z
	Small utility that displays the parameters of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.43</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:07:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinUAE 6.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winuae-4960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winuae-4960.html
</guid><description>
WinUAE is a port to Windows of emulator Amiga UAE are designed to simulate cargo Amore 500, 1000 and 2000. WinUAE is easily one of the emulator most complex that we have seen with more options than you can use. You will need to know where to find the resources to use it properly. It also supports multi-CPU simulation, drive, etc.
The characteristics of WinUAE
	The chips original (OCS), The chip enhanced (ECS) and architecture, advanced graphics (AGA)
	Device I / O: ( floppy drive ,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image 7.3 Build 7308</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:05:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz, etc.
R-Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download CpuFrequenz 4.48 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:05:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpufrequenz-2900.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpufrequenz-2900.html
</guid><description>
About the hardware, amount of RAM good, faster hard drives or solid state drives and multi-core processor is required to have better performance for your computer. About the software, you are not cluttered with the installed operating system to make it use the hardware with the highest performance.
If you feel the processor of the computer does not operate at full capacity even when you have good hardware, then it can be due to install the operating system, BIOS settings, error thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.8.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:04:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download xplorer2 Professional / Ultimate 6.2.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xplorer2-ultimate-1024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xplorer2-ultimate-1024.html
</guid><description>
Xplorer2 Ultimate is software, file manager replaces Windows explorer traditional with more advanced functions and flexibility. Xplorer2 Ultimate give the user the extension name space, such as FTP, zipprinters, webprinters, v. v. the model browser, find the ratio of good up large folders with thousands of files. Software, quick read, providing image filters and a variety of selection mechanism that allows you to manage your files effectively.
Xplorer2 Ultimate - file Management,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:01:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download ID Photos Pro 8.16.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-id-photos-pro-311.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-id-photos-pro-311.html
</guid><description>
ID Photos Pro is software professional is designed to handle the photo ID quickly and automatically (e.g. passport, Visa, etc.). ID Photos Pro built-in database with more than 281 format ID for more than 80 countries put ID Photos Pro 8.
Unlike photo editing software typical ID Photos Pro 8 has been developed specifically for the passport and photographic ID. This is why it is one of the tools the fastest and most accurate on the market today. Only need 10 seconds to download photos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.8.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ableton Live Suite 12.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:59:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html
</guid><description>
Ableton Live Suite is professional software to create, edit, music with effects, instruments, audio and all creative. Ableton Live Suite is the software fast, flexible and flexibility to create and perform music. Move freely between the musical elements and play with ideas, that don't stop the music and do not break the flow of your sound.
Features, Ableton Live Suite
	Meet Wavetable, Echo, Drum Buss and Pedal: the new equipment means new sounds, colorful can with the instruments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FontViewOK 8.99</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:58:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html
</guid><description>
FontViewOK is a simple tool that helps show your location and can install any fonts in list of it. To view (display) the font is not installed on Windows, you can also thanks to the help of Font View OK. Launch FontViewOK on the program screen, click the select folder Button From. Then just select the category to which the display font.
FontViewOK - Support install fonts
Many users install available font on Windows operating system of them and want tocompare the font visually on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Reader 2025.2.0.33046</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:57:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-reader-1898.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-reader-1898.html
</guid><description>
Foxit Reader is the software support people, office, create, edit and read PDF files, create notes, create a signature, set password protection and print PDF files quickly and easily. Foxit Reader is already supported on many different platforms on PC. Mac or Mobile, particularly on iPhone, Android with called Foxit MobilePDF, allowing reading material in many languages, this software creates a processing environment PDF convenient, moreover also is integrated with service cloud storage to...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioMaximus Pro 2.33.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:55:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiomaximus-pro-747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiomaximus-pro-747.html
</guid><description>
RadioMaximus Pro is a software support listen to the radio and record thousands of radio stations available on the Internet. When using the RadioMaximus Pro you will experience the ability to hear radio the most wonderful. The quality of radio is very good, there are many channels to choose from and the software continuously updates the news, latest music in the world to take to the listening station.
RadioMaximus Pro - Listen to the radio
Features RadioMaximus Pro
	Listen to and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:55:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.5.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:54:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.93</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:54:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image BootCD 7.3 Build 7308</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:53:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image BootCD is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v231</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:52:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download PTE Video Optimiser 1.0.2.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:52:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pte-video-optimiser-12839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pte-video-optimiser-12839.html
</guid><description>
Stabilize, reduce noise, crop, color correct, and more. Enjoy real-time instant previews of your edits and seamless batch processing for multiple files.
Video Stabilization
Our advanced stabilization technology analyzes every frame, corrects motion, and turns unsteady footage into smooth, cinematic-quality clips. Choose between two stabilization modes: Standard, for general use, and Camera Lock, which simulates tripod-like stabilization by keeping the frame steady and focused. Perfect...
</description></item><item><title>Download FBackup 9.9.987</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:52:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fbackup-1834.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fbackup-1834.html
</guid><description>
FBackup enables you to backup files and important folders on the hard drive locally or outside (not memory card, USB drive) or network drive. You can create multiple backup sets and schedule them to run automatically at the times defined in advance. The backups can be compressed into a ZIP file to be stored or reproduced in copy form files standard.
Modern interface
The program interface is quite easy to use, FBackup supports multi-language and provided the free utility, can also be...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.22.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:51:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item></channel></rss>